<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<posts>
  <row Id="1" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="3" CreationDate="2012-01-11T19:00:16.903" Score="24" ViewCount="127" Body="&lt;p&gt;Please give answers for HIV and/or other STD. I do understand that it depends on the risk groups (e.g. unprotected sex, males vs females, prostitution, homosexual sex, etc) so please provide as detailed information as possible. A lot of information on the web, literature, from GPs and sexual health clinics is contradicting each other.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="30" LastEditorUserId="25" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2012-01-11T20:10:33.257" LastActivityDate="2012-01-12T22:55:55.250" Title="How often should I get STI / STD testing done?" Tags="&lt;health&gt;&lt;std&gt;&lt;hiv&gt;&lt;safety&gt;" AnswerCount="2" CommentCount="5" />
  <row Id="2" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="1" CreationDate="2012-01-11T19:28:03.950" Score="4" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;I don't think there is any hard rule about when and what to get tested for. In general I've found that talking with my doctor and other trusted sources about I go for no less then 6 months with out being tested.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I do have other factors I take in to account, such as the style of my relationships. If they are monogamous I'm more willing to go longer between tests if I'm sure my partner is being honest with me. If I'm in a non-exclusive relationship I test more often, and if anything seems out of place &quot;down there&quot; on either me or my partner(s) I get tested right away and talk with my Doctor. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="40" LastEditorUserId="140" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2012-01-12T22:55:55.250" LastActivityDate="2012-01-12T22:55:55.250" />
  <row Id="3" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="1" CreationDate="2012-01-11T19:56:26.627" Score="23" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;6 months seems to be a consensus standard, and it's the one I apply (though I'm not sure about medical evidence).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Certain tests (like common HIV Antibody tests) have a &lt;a href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/HIV_test#Window_period&quot;&gt;&quot;window period&quot;&lt;/a&gt; where the test results may show a false negative, and a semi-annual test cycle cuts the time that you could be living with that false negative (and potentially putting partners at risk) in half when compared to an annual testing cycle.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;On a personal note, I have a few other testing checkpoints that I apply:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Any time something happens that exposes me to additional risk of infection&lt;br&gt;&#xA;(including any events &quot;outside the bedroom&quot;)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Any time I have any question about the STI/STD status of a partner.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;When entering into what will be a long-term relationship&lt;br&gt;&#xA;(and I ask the same of my partner).  &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;When a committed relationship ends.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="50" LastActivityDate="2012-01-11T19:56:26.627" />
  <row Id="4" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2012-01-11T20:02:12.327" Score="5" ViewCount="44" Body="&lt;p&gt;It's generally accepted that play with a TENS unit carries a certain amount of risk.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;That said, if one chooses to engage in such activities, what are the general guidelines to minimize severe and/or permanent harm during play?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I've often heard &quot;never do anything above the waist&quot; and that makes sense, given the proximity to the heart, but I was wondering if there were other guidelines that people follow in order to maximize safety (other than abstenance).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="41" LastEditorUserId="25" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2012-01-11T20:10:58.327" LastActivityDate="2012-01-12T21:43:54.003" Title="Commonly accepted guidelines to maximize safety with TENS units/electro-stimulus play" Tags="&lt;safety&gt;&lt;electro-stimulus&gt;" AnswerCount="1" FavoriteCount="1" />
  <row Id="5" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="96" CreationDate="2012-01-11T20:04:06.927" Score="7" ViewCount="101" Body="&lt;p&gt;It's a reality. Everyone or almost everyone in his adult life will hear repeatedly of the so called &lt;strong&gt;G-spot&lt;/strong&gt;. But I haven't yet known where it is in a reliable manner.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Can someone answer with something more specific? Are there any tips/techniques for finding and/or stimulating it?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="44" LastEditorUserId="13" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2012-01-12T21:16:37.577" LastActivityDate="2012-01-15T02:15:00.660" Title="Where is the G-Spot, exactly?" Tags="&lt;g-spot&gt;&lt;pleasure&gt;&lt;clitoris&gt;&lt;women&gt;" AnswerCount="3" CommentCount="6" />
  <row Id="6" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2012-01-11T20:05:29.280" Score="7" ViewCount="86" Body="&lt;p&gt;The question title says it all. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Is there a G-Spot in men? If there is, where?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I have not heard anything about this, so it is merely personal conjecture. But I don't think am the only one asking this question. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="44" LastActivityDate="2012-01-12T15:03:03.677" Title="Is there a G-Spot for men?" Tags="&lt;g-spot&gt;&lt;men&gt;" AnswerCount="1" />
  <row Id="7" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2012-01-11T20:12:16.647" Score="9" ViewCount="83" Body="&lt;p&gt;Since long ago sodomy has been practiced in many parts of the world. And many enjoy it, but is there a basis for this kind of pleasure? &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Is it a physical or psychological reaction. Physical as in the sexual organs or psychological as in behavior?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Both genders (in same-gender and non relationships) practice it as a successful form of coitus.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Can someone explain the source of this kind of pleasure?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="44" LastEditorUserId="41" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2012-01-11T20:57:52.033" LastActivityDate="2012-01-11T20:57:52.033" Title="Why is anal sex pleasurable?" Tags="&lt;pleasure&gt;&lt;sodomy&gt;&lt;anal-sex&gt;" AnswerCount="1" CommentCount="3" />
  <row Id="8" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2012-01-11T20:13:13.223" Score="6" ViewCount="65" Body="&lt;p&gt;Folks,&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I have major issues with premature ejaculation &lt;em&gt;and&lt;/em&gt; not being able to get an erection very often.  I know much of the latter is due to my psych medications -- and, sorry, suppressing bipolar is more important than my sex drive.  One of the best solutions to premature ejaculation is of course doing it more often, but that's an issue given the other problem :(&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;What else can I do to last longer than a minute? :(  She'd &lt;em&gt;really&lt;/em&gt; appreciate it!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="58" LastEditorUserId="25" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2012-01-11T20:24:51.617" LastActivityDate="2012-01-12T07:24:54.220" Title="How to increase male endurance?" Tags="&lt;health&gt;&lt;erectile-disfunction&gt;&lt;premature-ejactulation&gt;&lt;ejaculation&gt;&lt;sexual-dysfunction&gt;" AnswerCount="3" CommentCount="2" FavoriteCount="1" />
  <row Id="9" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="6" CreationDate="2012-01-11T20:16:47.710" Score="13" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;I'm not sure there's a direct equivalent, but two options spring immediately to mind:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The first is &lt;a href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Prostate_massage&quot;&gt;prostate stimulation&lt;/a&gt;. Mechanically think about the &quot;bend over and grab the table&quot; part of your physical, obviously with more of an erotic overtone than a clinical one.  This can be combined (or replaced) with external stimulation as well by pressing/rubbing on the perineum (&quot;taint&quot;) under/behind the scrotum. (Note that finding the &quot;right&quot; place to press/rub here might be as difficult as locating the female G-Spot, particularly if you opt for the anal route rather than the external one - It will take some practice, and may cause some discomfort until you know what you're doing so be careful/gentle!)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The other is that the underside of the glans tends to be extremely sensitive on most men, particularly to light touch.  It can be pleasurable for some people, though I know others who become hyper-stimulated and overly sensitive, which makes it more uncomfortable than enjoyable.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Of course whether or not either of these is something your partner will enjoy is something you'll have to work out for yourselves.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="50" LastEditorUserId="117" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2012-01-12T15:03:03.677" LastActivityDate="2012-01-12T15:03:03.677" CommentCount="3" />
  <row Id="10" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2012-01-11T20:16:52.350" Score="0" ViewCount="57" Body="&lt;p&gt;Is there a reliable procedure or treatment to deal with this problem?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="44" LastEditorUserId="25" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2012-01-11T20:22:24.630" LastActivityDate="2012-01-11T20:49:59.100" ClosedDate="2012-01-11T21:04:30.617" Title="How to deal with erectile disfunction?" Tags="&lt;erectile-disfunction&gt;&lt;treatment&gt;&lt;health&gt;&lt;men&gt;&lt;penis&gt;" AnswerCount="1" CommentCount="3" />
  <row Id="11" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2012-01-11T20:18:57.753" Score="3" ViewCount="52" Body="&lt;p&gt;Almost 3 years ago my wife and i began using vibrators to stimulate her clitoris while we have intercourse. Sex &quot;quality&quot; with those toys is great, but after some time it seems as if we need more powerful or intense toys for her to reach climax.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Is there any risk to get &quot;addicted&quot; to these toys to the point where sex without them can become &quot;boring&quot;?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="54" LastEditorUserId="25" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2012-01-11T20:24:23.020" LastActivityDate="2012-01-11T20:29:45.573" Title="Reliance on sexual toys/fetishes" Tags="&lt;toys&gt;&lt;long-term-relationships&gt;&lt;fetish&gt;&lt;sexual-dysfunction&gt;" AnswerCount="1" />
  <row Id="12" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="8" CreationDate="2012-01-11T20:19:35.793" Score="6" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;According to &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.tandfonline.com/doi/abs/10.1080/00926239608405302&quot;&gt;this study&lt;/a&gt;, Kegel exercises have been shown to help reduce premature ejaculation in men. For a lighter read and more general information on Kegel exercises, checkout the &lt;a href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Kegel_exercise&quot;&gt;Kegel exercise wikipedia article&lt;/a&gt;, (from which I obtained the link to the study given above), specifically the section on &lt;a href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Kegel_exercise#Sexual_function&quot;&gt;sexual function&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="39" LastEditorUserId="39" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2012-01-11T20:25:49.107" LastActivityDate="2012-01-11T20:25:49.107" CommentCount="2" />
  <row Id="13" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2012-01-11T20:21:43.243" Score="-2" ViewCount="78" Body="&lt;p&gt;What non-human animals have homosexual intercourse, and how frequently is this seen? Are some species more prone to homosexual behavior than others?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="25" LastActivityDate="2012-01-11T20:21:43.243" ClosedDate="2012-01-11T20:46:27.830" Title="Homosexuality in the Animal Kingdom" Tags="&lt;homosexuality&gt;&lt;animals&gt;" CommentCount="3" />
  <row Id="14" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="7" CreationDate="2012-01-11T20:23:02.060" Score="11" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;The anal opening contains a lot of different nerve-endings which, when stimulated, can be pleasurable. Then there is also the G-spot and prostate that, depending on sex can be stimulated from anal penetration, prostate because it's basically the easiest way to reach the prostate through the rectum and the G-spot because there is a only a very thin membrane between the rectum and the vagina.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Of course there is also the psychological sensation attributed to it which probably is what attracts most heterosexuals to it since it is both taboo and can be a way of expressing dominance/submission.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="61" LastActivityDate="2012-01-11T20:23:02.060" />
  <row Id="15" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="8" CreationDate="2012-01-11T20:25:50.383" Score="-1" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;Although i'm no professional expert, intercourse isn't the only way to give your companion pleasure. From my personal experience, vibrators for her clitoris can do wonders, and you can penetrate her meanwhile she uses the vibrator to stimulate her clitoris. Also, try slowing down your rythm and/or end coitus before you ejaculate, calm down, repeat.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You can also try to invert the equation here: stimulate her so hard, she will come to climax faster than you.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="54" LastActivityDate="2012-01-11T20:25:50.383" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="16" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="11" CreationDate="2012-01-11T20:29:45.573" Score="4" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;As for physical sensation there is no proof that this would cause any permanent desensitation of her clitoris. (&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.goaskalice.columbia.edu/3757.html&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;Source&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you feel that the increasing demand on power and intensity is becoming too high just back off for a while, stop using toys or use significantly lower power. This might be frustrating but quickly increases sensitivity again.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="61" LastActivityDate="2012-01-11T20:29:45.573" CommentCount="2" />
  <row Id="17" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="10" CreationDate="2012-01-11T20:49:59.100" Score="0" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;Without having a medical degree, I think that it depends on the root cause of the problem, if the cause is a mental conditon I can probably be reliably treated with therapy. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="55" LastActivityDate="2012-01-11T20:49:59.100" />
  <row Id="18" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="27" CreationDate="2012-01-11T20:59:13.810" Score="11" ViewCount="130" Body="&lt;p&gt;Common answers include: &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Are you using enough lube? - Yes.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Is the top hung like a donkey? - No.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Are you relaxed? - Yes&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Then why does it still hurt like &lt;em&gt;buggery&lt;/em&gt;? &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="75" LastEditorUserId="21" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2012-01-11T22:29:41.570" LastActivityDate="2012-01-13T15:53:09.513" Title="Why does anal sex hurt?" Tags="&lt;anal-sex&gt;" AnswerCount="4" CommentCount="3" />
  <row Id="19" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="127" CreationDate="2012-01-11T21:12:11.980" Score="18" ViewCount="91" Body="&lt;p&gt;I have read a lot of texts about female ejaculation but I have yet to find any conclusion on what the fluid is, where it comes from and what function it has. So my question is: What does the latest studies tell us about female ejaculation?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="61" LastActivityDate="2012-01-16T01:11:56.757" Title="What does female ejaculate contain?" Tags="&lt;ejaculation&gt;&lt;female&gt;&lt;orgasm&gt;&lt;secretion&gt;" AnswerCount="2" FavoriteCount="1" />
  <row Id="20" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="18" CreationDate="2012-01-11T21:12:34.100" Score="2" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;I think the issue here is you are going straight for sex. Don't start with full blown sex, try with a finger or a very small vibrator. After a few sessions you can start to build up to larger toys. Only try full blown sex when you are comfotable masterbating with a penis sized object. Even then take it slow and start with something small to get you ready. With anal, the best way to avoid hurting is to take it slow and use lots of lube&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="48" LastActivityDate="2012-01-11T21:12:34.100" />
  <row Id="21" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="18" CreationDate="2012-01-11T21:15:30.540" Score="1" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;Well the humorous answer would be because it &lt;em&gt;is&lt;/em&gt; buggery...&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In seriousness the answer is probably similar to &quot;Why is vaginal intercourse painful the first time?&quot; -- A new sensation that your body isn't prepared for, combined with tissues that are not normally accustomed to stretching, or at least not for the length of time anal sex would last.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To reduce the chance of pain (and injury) some &quot;warm up&quot; exercises may be in order, using fingers or toys.  Also consider trying other lubricants:  there are many brands, and many different properties.  The original water-based Astroglide is known for its lubricity and resistance to drying out.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="50" LastActivityDate="2012-01-11T21:15:30.540" CommentCount="5" />
  <row Id="22" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="26" CreationDate="2012-01-11T21:19:51.797" Score="3" ViewCount="61" Body="&lt;p&gt;Circumcision is a common practice in many countries in the world, but it is mostly performed due to social and cultural reasons (religious tradition, &quot;wanting the boy to look like his father&quot;, etc.).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;What are some other reasons one might choose to be circumcised, or have their child undergo the procedure?&lt;br&gt;&#xA;What are some of the drawbacks one needs to consider before undergoing the procedure?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="60" LastEditorUserId="60" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2012-01-12T10:03:09.887" LastActivityDate="2012-01-12T10:03:09.887" Title="What are the benefits and drawback of circumcision?" Tags="&lt;men&gt;&lt;penis&gt;&lt;circumcision&gt;" AnswerCount="1" CommentCount="5" />
  <row Id="23" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="18" CreationDate="2012-01-11T21:20:00.250" Score="1" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;The problem is probably tensing up too much because of fear or insecurity, relaxing and being turned on is just as, or even more, important than lube (lube is still required in most cases tho).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="61" LastActivityDate="2012-01-11T21:20:00.250" />
  <row Id="24" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="106" CreationDate="2012-01-11T21:23:51.840" Score="2" ViewCount="68" Body="&lt;p&gt;Are there any techniques of male masturbation one can't perform as well or at all after being circumcised? This would include techniques that require the so called &quot;gliding mechanism&quot; of the foreskin for example.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="60" LastEditorUserId="17" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2012-01-13T19:01:30.313" LastActivityDate="2012-01-15T16:40:39.680" Title="How does circumcision affect masturbation?" Tags="&lt;men&gt;&lt;penis&gt;&lt;circumcision&gt;&lt;masturbation&gt;&lt;foreskin&gt;" AnswerCount="3" />
  <row Id="25" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2012-01-11T21:29:03.120" Score="7" ViewCount="92" Body="&lt;p&gt;We've all heard the old wives tale that if you masturbate too much, you'll go blind. But in all seriousness, are there any medical detriments to masturbation (either short term or long term)? On the flip side, are there any medical benefits? When I say medical, I mean both from a physical and psychological perspective.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="39" LastEditorUserId="171" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2012-01-16T10:48:40.950" LastActivityDate="2012-01-17T00:39:31.167" Title="Medical detriments/benefits of masturbation" Tags="&lt;masturbation&gt;&lt;health&gt;" AnswerCount="5" CommentCount="5" />
  <row Id="26" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="22" CreationDate="2012-01-11T21:29:41.350" Score="2" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;Outside of religious/cultural reasons or treating specific medical conditions (phimosis or paraphimosis where alternative options haven't worked) I'm not aware of any medical benefits to circumcision.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Potential drawbacks of the procedure that I'm aware of include a &quot;tight&quot; circumcision that makes a full erection painful, and eventually a decrease in sensitivity (the body becomes accustomed to friction on the glans and &quot;ignores&quot; the sensation).&lt;br&gt;&#xA;Additionally if the procedure is performed as an adult the healing time is longer (or maybe it just feels longer as both intercourse and masturbation are not options while the penis is healing).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For more comprehensive information you may want to speak to a doctor.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="50" LastEditorUserId="50" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2012-01-12T06:15:51.650" LastActivityDate="2012-01-12T06:15:51.650" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="27" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="18" CreationDate="2012-01-11T21:30:33.667" Score="12" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://anexperimentintruth.blogspot.com/2012/01/bottoming-101.html&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;Bottoming 101&lt;/a&gt;: A good primer on how to bottom and get pleasure out of it, from a man with experience...&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It's a very long blog post, and very extensive, so here are a few bullet points relevant to the question:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;It will probably hurt initially. Depending on practice it will get easier&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Your anal sphincters are muscles, and much like any muscle in the body they can be trained, and can be overstretched or abused.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Patience is key, take your time, it's not a race or a contest. Make sure the person who is inserting whatever into your anus also understands this. It's OK to stop and start.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Relax. One of your two anal sphincters is involuntary, so you need to subconsciously allow yourself to submit to the penetration. If you're uptight, or worried, or convinced it's gonna hurt then it will, so just let things happen, and take it easy. Take all the time you need.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Try focussing on breathing, it will clear your mind and you'll stop worrying so much on what's happening down there. Exhale when things go in.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Try to become more aware of what your anal muscles are doing, maybe perform some visualisation exercises&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;If it hurts whilst penetrating, hold it there, don't try to push it out.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Practice makes perfect&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;And finally and most importantly:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;It's OK to not be a bottom, there is no social norm that say you have to be one, some people just naturally can't cope with things up there. Maybe you're just one of them.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="80" LastEditorUserId="145" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2012-01-13T15:53:09.513" LastActivityDate="2012-01-13T15:53:09.513" CommentCount="3" />
  <row Id="28" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="38" CreationDate="2012-01-11T21:32:20.737" Score="4" ViewCount="45" Body="&lt;p&gt;As &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=waO8KKtVgaQ&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;Yossi Vardi called it, &quot;local warming&quot;&lt;/a&gt; is a term meaning overheating of testicles by for example putting laptops over one's lap an using it for an extended period of time.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As we all know, in order to produce sperm the testicles need to be kept cooler than one's internal body heat. If they are kept at a higher temperature, one's sperm count goes down. Being frequently exposed to local warming, I am wondering if this effect is temporary, or more permanent? For example, if one was to overheat one's testicles for a long amount of time and later stop, will the sperm count go back to normal, or be in some way hampered for life?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="60" LastActivityDate="2012-01-12T09:26:39.390" Title="&quot;Local warming&quot; and long-term effects" Tags="&lt;men&gt;&lt;sperm&gt;&lt;testicles&gt;&lt;scrotum&gt;&lt;heat&gt;" AnswerCount="1" />
  <row Id="29" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="25" CreationDate="2012-01-11T21:37:47.890" Score="9" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;Benefits of masturbation:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Stress and sexual tension relief&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/10333355?dopt=Abstract&quot;&gt;Is an enjoyable activity, so it produces dopamine in the brain&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Lowering testosterone level&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://humrep.oxfordjournals.org/content/12/10/2200.abstract?maxtoshow=&amp;amp;HITS=10&amp;amp;hits=10&amp;amp;RESULTFORMAT=1&amp;amp;andorexacttitle=and&amp;amp;andorexacttitleabs=and&amp;amp;andorexactfulltext=and&amp;amp;searchid=1&amp;amp;FIRSTINDEX=0&amp;amp;sortspec=relevance&amp;amp;volume=12&amp;amp;firstpage=2200&amp;amp;resourcetype=HWCIT&quot;&gt;Helps boost the immune system&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/15069045?dopt=Abstract&quot;&gt;Might help prevent prostate cancer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://books.nap.edu/openbook.php?record_id=9934&amp;amp;page=119&quot;&gt;Can help with insomnia&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Detriments of masturbation:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Temporary lower sperm count (as it needs to be replenished with time)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Possible consequences depending on what the act of masturbation involves (for example, autoerotic asphyxiation and the possibility of choking)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="60" LastEditorUserId="60" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2012-01-11T22:15:34.600" LastActivityDate="2012-01-11T22:15:34.600" CommentCount="6" />
  <row Id="30" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2012-01-11T21:39:24.413" Score="1" ViewCount="31" Body="&lt;p&gt;I have been tempted to buy an electro kit for a while. What has been holding me back if the lack of decent reviews, when spending ~£200 for a kit I want to know i'm buying a good item and that I will enjoy the experience. Can anyone recommend a good resource to help me pick a good kit?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="48" LastActivityDate="2012-01-11T21:39:24.413" ClosedDate="2012-01-14T12:33:12.060" Title="Good objective reviews of electro sex toys" Tags="&lt;electro-stimulus&gt;" CommentCount="3" />
  <row Id="31" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2012-01-11T21:43:16.997" Score="1" ViewCount="62" Body="&lt;p&gt;How can you warm a &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.lovehoney.co.uk/product.cfm?p=14734&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;Tenga Masturbator&lt;/a&gt;? There was for a brief period a warming item available but you can't buy that in the UK any longer (to my knowledge). I have tried bathing the device in warm water; that feels nice but soon cools to room temperature. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="48" LastEditorUserId="108" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2012-01-12T03:41:30.830" LastActivityDate="2012-01-12T06:39:52.547" Title="Warming a Tenga Masturbator" Tags="&lt;masturbation&gt;&lt;toys&gt;" AnswerCount="1" CommentCount="2" />
  <row Id="32" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="25" CreationDate="2012-01-11T21:50:05.927" Score="1" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;Long term medical disadvantages of masturbation : None (unless you're using a dangerous toy or practice)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Long term medical advantages of masturbation : &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1046/j.1464-410X.2003.04319.x/abstract&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;Reduced prostate cancer risk&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Relieves stress (releases hormones)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Physical exercise&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="48" LastEditorUserId="140" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2012-01-16T03:43:51.707" LastActivityDate="2012-01-16T03:43:51.707" />
  <row Id="33" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="36" CreationDate="2012-01-11T21:53:32.207" Score="7" ViewCount="78" Body="&lt;p&gt;I remember hearing a while back that Freud had a number of theories about the origins of a persons fetishes. However, I also know that while Freud made a number of good contributions to the world of psychology, he was also a perverted old man at times (dream interpretations). Is there any modern understanding for the psychological (or heck, who knows, biological, genetic, etc.) origins of a person's fetishes?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If so, listing some readings on the material I feel would be very interesting.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="31" LastActivityDate="2012-01-15T19:00:18.593" Title="Origin of a fetish" Tags="&lt;fetish&gt;&lt;psychology&gt;&lt;freud&gt;" AnswerCount="2" FavoriteCount="1" />
  <row Id="34" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="73" CreationDate="2012-01-11T21:59:18.067" Score="11" ViewCount="126" Body="&lt;p&gt;There seems to be a variety of physical signs many females conform to when they achieve orgasms. Those would include things like erection of nipples, muscle tensing up and the like. Is there a list of those physicals signs that most women exhibit when they climax, and if so, which ones could be &quot;opted-out&quot; with enough practice (for example, can a woman achieve an orgasm without tensing up)?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="60" LastEditorUserId="17" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2012-01-12T21:54:03.130" LastActivityDate="2012-01-12T21:54:03.130" Title="What are the common physical signs of a female orgasm?" Tags="&lt;female&gt;&lt;orgasm&gt;&lt;symptoms&gt;" AnswerCount="2" CommentCount="2" FavoriteCount="1" />
  <row Id="35" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="25" CreationDate="2012-01-11T21:59:46.007" Score="5" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;There seems to be some connection between frequent masturbation in males between 20-30 and prostate cancer (&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.livescience.com/7658-masturbation-increase-risk-prostate-cancer.html&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;Source&lt;/a&gt;). But from my reading of the articles about it, the connection could as well be that high sex-drive and a high risk for prostate cancer is the more relevant connection.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As for the positive effects you have a lot of &quot;feel-good hormones&quot; going through your body during orgasm which can help with stress and tensions. For men using &quot;edging&quot; (that is stimulating until close to orgasm, backing off and then repeating) is also said to help increase sexual stamina and endurance during sex, I do not know if this could also help females with premature-orgasms.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Also for both male and females, masturbation can help a lot when it comes to knowing ones own body and being comfortable with it.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="61" LastEditorUserId="61" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2012-01-11T22:10:28.890" LastActivityDate="2012-01-11T22:10:28.890" CommentCount="3" />
  <row Id="36" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="33" CreationDate="2012-01-11T22:07:47.567" Score="3" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;Short answer is nobody knows. Human psychology is such a complex subject, and we know so little that any discussion on the cause of fetishes is basically guess work. Their have been links suggested between childhood experiences and fetishes but there is no substantial evidence (to my knowledge) to back up that claim. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="48" LastActivityDate="2012-01-11T22:07:47.567" />
  <row Id="37" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="34" CreationDate="2012-01-11T22:16:57.240" Score="3" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;Increased blood flow and muscles tensing up is basically the most sure signs of orgasm in both male and female, the muscle tension does not need to come until seconds right before the climax. Increased blood flow on chest, neck and face is probably the most obvious signs depending on complexion.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="61" LastActivityDate="2012-01-11T22:16:57.240" />
  <row Id="38" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="28" CreationDate="2012-01-11T22:27:14.370" Score="2" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;Unless severely increase in temperature for a long time (scalding your testicles for a long time?) the effect is very temporary.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A &lt;a href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Heat-based_contraception&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;natural heat-based male contraceptive method&lt;/a&gt; is based on this fact and is in short term fully reversible. There seems to be very few, if any, studies done on the long term effects tho.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="61" LastEditorUserId="61" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2012-01-12T09:26:39.390" LastActivityDate="2012-01-12T09:26:39.390" />
  <row Id="39" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2012-01-11T22:43:07.107" Score="1" ViewCount="41" Body="&lt;p&gt;Are there any good websites one can rely on providing objective review of sexual toys? Obviously one could try going onto various sex shop website and see what items are promoted or have good reviews, but those might be biased (store wanting to sell the expensive, gimmicky items, rather than the good ones), or subjective (someone's initial reaction to the toy purchased).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="60" LastActivityDate="2012-01-11T22:43:07.107" ClosedDate="2012-01-12T22:51:24.683" Title="Objective sexual toy review websites" Tags="&lt;toys&gt;&lt;reviews&gt;&lt;stores&gt;&lt;shopping&gt;&lt;guide&gt;" CommentCount="5" FavoriteCount="0" />
  <row Id="40" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2012-01-11T23:41:52.763" Score="8" ViewCount="85" Body="&lt;p&gt;What are the physical sensation differences between &quot;bareback&quot; (unprotected) and sex with a condom? Do condoms increase or decrease pleasure? Is there more stimulation to either partner with one or the other? Why? &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Let us exclude psychological (condom anxiety / excitement from bareback sex) and practical (erection loss during putting the condom on) differences.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I'm asking about both top and bottom perspectives, for both anal and vaginal intercourse.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="30" LastEditorUserId="17" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2012-01-12T02:27:18.193" LastActivityDate="2012-01-12T15:02:55.440" Title="How does using a condom affect the way sex feels?" Tags="&lt;pleasure&gt;&lt;anal-sex&gt;&lt;condom&gt;" AnswerCount="2" />
  <row Id="41" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="42" CreationDate="2012-01-12T00:07:51.550" Score="7" ViewCount="34" Body="&lt;p&gt;If so, why is that ? Are tips to help females to deal with it ?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="47" LastEditorUserId="108" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2012-01-12T02:51:40.347" LastActivityDate="2012-01-12T02:51:40.347" Title="Does birth control pills/injections decreases female sexual appetite?" Tags="&lt;female&gt;&lt;birth-control&gt;" AnswerCount="1" CommentCount="1" FavoriteCount="1" />
  <row Id="42" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="41" CreationDate="2012-01-12T00:35:18.163" Score="9" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.epigee.org/guide/pill_sex.html&quot;&gt;This article&lt;/a&gt; explains what a study on birth control pill on female's libido has found. In short:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;[T]his study finds that women using the birth control pill showed markedly-decreased levels of sexual desire than those women who do not use the birth control pill. It also found that women who had discontinued use of the pill continued to suffer side effects in the long-term.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So yes, birth control pills decrease the libido, even after the female stops taking the pill.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;One recommendation for females mentioned in the article is:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;If you are finding that you are experiencing the effects of a low libido, you may want to speak to your health care provider.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Which is probably the wisest thing to do with most if not all such problems.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="60" LastActivityDate="2012-01-12T00:35:18.163" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="43" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="40" CreationDate="2012-01-12T02:39:18.623" Score="8" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;A condom on the penis reduces the direct stimulation of friction to the penis, which can reduce sensation and delay orgasm. Different condoms can feel different, so gather empirical data (in the obvious way). For men that orgasm sooner than they would like, common advice is to use a condom to reduce sensation. Don't assume this means that sex with a condom is always less enjoyable than sex without.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A great deal of the experience of sex is psychological. If you're really excited to be engaging in this sex, you'll probably orgasm sooner, regardless of condom. If the idea of &quot;barebacking&quot; is exciting to you, wearing a condom may be disappointing, but if the idea of unprotected sex is scary, because risk of STD or pregnancy, wearing a condom can increase enjoyment. Some people associate condom use with &quot;cheating&quot; which may add to the excitement. This is all very specific to the people involved and the exact context, so there is no universal answer.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For a female partner during vaginal intercourse, a condom can change the way things feel in a way that may be significant, and possibly less pleasurable. (I assume this is also true for anal sex, but I don't have the data on hand). This is also highly personal. Since the texture of latex is different than the texture of a penis, ease of penetration can be affected; the use of a lubricant can compensate.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It bears repeating that certain lubricants are not appropriate for use with a latex condom, notably petroleum jelly (Vaseline) and other oil-based lubricants.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In some people, the delicate genital tissues can react badly to the latex in most condoms, from a minor decrease in pleasure to a significant allergic reaction. For those with latex allergies, a non-latex condom can be a good choice.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="17" LastEditorUserId="117" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2012-01-12T15:02:55.440" LastActivityDate="2012-01-12T15:02:55.440" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="44" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="49" CreationDate="2012-01-12T03:01:13.940" Score="12" ViewCount="84" Body="&lt;p&gt;It is widely known that females can achieve multiple orgasms in a short period of time. It is less known that males are also said to be able to do the same.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;What should one do in order to experience multiple orgasms as a guy?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="60" LastActivityDate="2012-01-16T01:50:03.227" Title="How can a guy experience multiple orgasms?" Tags="&lt;orgasm&gt;&lt;male&gt;&lt;multiple-orgasms&gt;" AnswerCount="3" FavoriteCount="1" />
  <row Id="45" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="78" CreationDate="2012-01-12T03:18:10.330" Score="10" ViewCount="99" Body="&lt;p&gt;&quot;&lt;a href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Furry_fandom&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;The furry fandom&lt;/a&gt; is a fandom for fictional anthropomorphic animal characters with human personalities and characteristics.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;According to &lt;a href=&quot;http://studyf3.livejournal.com/1383.html&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;the study done by the University of California&lt;/a&gt;, &quot;19–25% of the fandom members report homosexuality, 37–48% bisexuality, 30–51% heterosexual, and 3–8% other forms of alternative sexual relationships&quot;. In comparison to the study done by &lt;a href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/LGBT_demographics_of_the_United_States&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;National Survey of Sexual Health and Behavior&lt;/a&gt;, in the USA population &quot;7 percent of women and 8 percent of men identify as gay, lesbian or bisexual&quot;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Are there any studies that explain why the furry fandom has such high rates of people declaring non-heterosexual orientation, in comparison to the average from USA, where the fandom seems to be most popular?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="60" LastEditorUserId="123" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2012-01-12T15:03:07.513" LastActivityDate="2012-01-12T21:19:17.620" Title="Furry fandom and the high rates of non-heterosexual orientation" Tags="&lt;homosexuality&gt;&lt;furry&gt;&lt;sexual-orientation&gt;&lt;survey&gt;&lt;bisexuality&gt;" AnswerCount="2" CommentCount="3" />
  <row Id="46" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2012-01-12T03:26:06.033" Score="12" ViewCount="82" Body="&lt;p&gt;Many sex acts can be physically demanding. If one partner is out of shape, they may become exhausted before both partners are fully satisfied. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;What are some techniques for helping these couples accommodate their limitations?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;(Let us ignore regular aerobic exercise to increase physical endurance, as that isn't an accommodation for current physical condition, but a way to adjust that condition. And maybe sex is their aerobic exercise of choice.)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="17" LastEditorUserId="15" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2012-01-17T15:18:45.280" LastActivityDate="2012-01-17T15:18:45.280" Title="How to compensate during sex for low physical endurance?" Tags="&lt;health&gt;&lt;accommodation&gt;" AnswerCount="1" FavoriteCount="0" />
  <row Id="47" PostTypeId="5" CreationDate="2012-01-12T03:50:04.060" Score="0" ViewCount="1" Body="" OwnerUserId="-1" LastEditorUserId="-1" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2012-01-12T03:50:04.060" LastActivityDate="2012-01-12T03:50:04.060" />
  <row Id="48" PostTypeId="4" CreationDate="2012-01-12T03:50:04.060" Score="0" ViewCount="" Body="Electro-stimulus is the use of electric charges applied directly to the body." OwnerUserId="-1" LastEditorUserId="17" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2012-01-12T04:10:54.337" LastActivityDate="2012-01-12T04:10:54.337" />
  <row Id="49" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="44" CreationDate="2012-01-12T03:55:38.310" Score="9" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;While each person's sexual response is different, males tend to need a break called a &quot;&lt;a href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Refractory_period_%28sex%29&quot;&gt;refractory period&lt;/a&gt;&quot; averaging 1/2 an hour, while most women are able to continue to enjoy sex after the first orgasm (barring soreness).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There's a book that offers to teach men to have multiple orgasms, entitled &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://rads.stackoverflow.com/amzn/click/0062513362&quot;&gt;The Multi-Orgasmic Man&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="17" LastActivityDate="2012-01-12T03:55:38.310" />
  <row Id="50" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2012-01-12T04:00:28.283" Score="6" ViewCount="47" Body="&lt;p&gt;In situations where a condom with spermicidal lubricant is used and the intercourse does not end after the condom is used, there are opportunities for the spermicidal lubricant to be consumed.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Aside from being potentially unpleasant, are there any known side-effects or harmful long term effects from ingesting spermicide from lubricant?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="41" LastActivityDate="2012-01-16T18:14:03.097" Title="Are there any harmful side-effects to ingesting spermicidal lubricant?" Tags="&lt;condom&gt;&lt;birth-control&gt;&lt;spermicidal-lubricant&gt;" AnswerCount="2" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="52" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2012-01-12T05:29:50.073" Score="4" ViewCount="31" Body="&lt;p&gt;Assuming psychological causes can be ruled out, what typically causes erectile dysfunction?  What would be possible ways of telling what cause?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="115" LastEditorUserId="124" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2012-01-12T12:58:27.140" LastActivityDate="2012-01-12T16:46:26.253" Title="What are common physical causes of erectile dysfunction?" Tags="&lt;sexual-dysfunction&gt;&lt;man&gt;" AnswerCount="1" />
  <row Id="53" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="31" CreationDate="2012-01-12T06:39:52.547" Score="1" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.lovehoney.co.uk/product.cfm?p=17726&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;Tenga Hole Warmer&lt;/a&gt; is still available from the same site you linked to.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Barring the availability of that item you can ask at a local brick-and-mortar &quot;sex shop&quot; (if you have one in your area) to see if they have something similar that they know works with the Tenga.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;You might be able to get a similar sensation with a &quot;warming&quot; lubricant like &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.k-y.com/WARMING_Liquid&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;K-Y Warming Liquid&lt;/a&gt; (or &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.k-y.com/Warming_Jelly&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;Jelly&lt;/a&gt; if you prefer).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If a warming lubricant doesn't work for you and the &quot;Tenga Hole Warmer&quot; isn't available you may have another option, though I would &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;not&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; recommend this: Looking at the product description the Tenga Hole Warmer seems to be a snap-activated exothermic device (fancy way of saying it's bascally a glowstick that gets hot instead of lighting up).  You &lt;em&gt;may&lt;/em&gt; be able to achieve similar results using other chemical heating devices (like hand warmers).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;code&gt;BIG IMPORTANT WARNING AND DISCLAIMER&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;  I have never tried using another kind of heating device (I don't own a Tenga).  &lt;em&gt;It is possible that other heating devices may create unsafe temperatures and cause serious injury&lt;/em&gt;.  It will definitely void any kind of warranty on the Tenga.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;  &lt;strong&gt;TEST EXTENSIVELY&lt;/strong&gt; (use a toy to compress the material inside the Tenga, let the heating device warm up to its hottest point, and then feel the inside with your fingers to ensure it is at a safe temperature with no major &quot;hot spots&quot; before putting anything more sensitive in there) and be prepared to stop using the device in a hurry if you experience any discomfort.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="50" LastActivityDate="2012-01-12T06:39:52.547" />
  <row Id="54" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="46" CreationDate="2012-01-12T07:09:04.137" Score="10" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;The best technique I can think of is variety: In any kind of physically demanding sexual activity there are usually two (or more) people involved, and it is not always necessary for one partner to be &quot;doing all the work&quot;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As an example, assuming basic missionary position the partner &quot;on top&quot; will be doing the majority of the physical activity.  If that partner begins to tire changing positions to allow the other partner to &quot;ride&quot; them will allow a rest, and give the other partner an opportunity to take a more active role.  (Note that from experience I can tell you that coordinating such position shifts may require some practice!)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Another option in the Variety toolbox is switching up the activity: Cuddling, heavy petting, (mutual) masturbation and oral sex can offer a break from the higher-intensity physical activity while retaining the intimacy and contact associated with sex.  &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Additional activity options are available if one or more of the participants are agreeable to the use of toys: Conventional activities tend to involve core and leg muscles more so than the upper body, and those muscle groups can get a rest while pleasuring your partner with a dildo or masturbation sleeve.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="50" LastActivityDate="2012-01-12T07:09:04.137" CommentCount="2" />
  <row Id="55" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="8" CreationDate="2012-01-12T07:24:54.220" Score="5" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;In addition to Kurtis' advice there are some other options that come to mind:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Using a condom can reduce the sensation of friction, and may help delay orgasm.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Most condom manufacturers produce at least one line of condoms with an anaesthetic lubricant (Trojan's are called &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.trojancondoms.com/Product/trojan-extended-pleasure-condoms-with-climax-control-lubricant.aspx&quot;&gt;Extended Pleasure&lt;/a&gt; with &quot;climax control&quot; lubricant)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;You can speak to your doctor about a topical anaesthetic. &#xA;(Note that if you go this route you may want to wear a condom over the anaesthetic to prevent numbing your partner and delaying &lt;em&gt;her&lt;/em&gt; climax as well)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="50" LastActivityDate="2012-01-12T07:24:54.220" />
  <row Id="56" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2012-01-12T07:40:27.347" Score="3" ViewCount="92" Body="&lt;p&gt;As a musician I sometimes find that having music on while having sex can enhance the experience, doing anything from providing a rhythm to match while thrusting to just enhancing the overall experience by lending a different atmosphere/ambiance/mood.  (Also the lyrics to some songs can be quite &quot;encouraging&quot;.)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;How common is this? In particular, is anyone aware of research/studies involving music during sex?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I would be particularly interested in any studies correlating certain musical genres, bands/songs, or orchestral works with arousal and/or sexual satisfaction.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;Assumptions: Sexual activity taking place in private (i.e. not having sex at a concert)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="50" LastEditorUserId="17" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2012-01-14T17:19:27.143" LastActivityDate="2012-01-15T14:23:40.147" Title="How common is music during sex?" Tags="&lt;music&gt;&lt;sexual-practices&gt;" AnswerCount="2" CommentCount="5" />
  <row Id="57" PostTypeId="5" CreationDate="2012-01-12T07:45:35.793" Score="0" ViewCount="1" Body="&lt;p&gt;This tag is for questions with broad applicability to a wide range of sexual practices.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;Unless the Wherever possible please use a more specific tag such as the ones listed below:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/questions/tagged/anal-sex&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'anal-sex'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;anal-sex&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;a href=&quot;/questions/tagged/vaginal-sex&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'vaginal-sex'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;vaginal-sex&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;&lt;a href=&quot;/questions/tagged/oral-sex&quot; class=&quot;post-tag&quot; title=&quot;show questions tagged 'oral-sex'&quot; rel=&quot;tag&quot;&gt;oral-sex&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="-1" LastEditorUserId="50" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2012-01-12T15:03:42.350" LastActivityDate="2012-01-12T15:03:42.350" />
  <row Id="58" PostTypeId="4" CreationDate="2012-01-12T07:45:35.793" Score="0" ViewCount="" Body="Questions regarding sex acts in general, with broad applicability. Questions using this tag should not be specific to oral, anal or vaginal sex -- please use a more specific tag if your question is not broadly applicable to a wide range of sexual practices." OwnerUserId="-1" LastEditorUserId="50" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2012-01-12T15:03:54.627" LastActivityDate="2012-01-12T15:03:54.627" />
  <row Id="59" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="40" CreationDate="2012-01-12T08:22:47.357" Score="3" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;The feeling during sex with a condom seems, based on opinions I've seen expressed, to vary quite dramatically from person to person.  However, there are also many different styles of condoms which may impact the feel from person to person.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;One common difference is materials: latex, non-latex, natural...  I used to have a friend who swore that natural condoms felt quite a lot better, though I never found that to be the case.  Caveat: Natural condoms do not do as good a job of STD prevention.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;What I've found to be a bigger difference is the shape and lubrication.  Dry lubrication or powdered condoms I find to not feel as good as wet lubricated condoms.  There are also different shapes, for example the Inspiral condoms have a larger end which I find produces more sensation than tighter-fitting shapes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Be aware of allergies to both the material and lubrication.  Particularly mild allergies which don't show obvious signs such as breaking out, but may cause minor irritation and may impact enjoyment of one or both parties.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Personally, I've found that condoms really don't detract from the pleasure of sex.  Whenever I've heard someone say &quot;it just doesn't &lt;strong&gt;feel&lt;/strong&gt; as good, I've always thought to myself &quot;C'mon, it feels pretty darn good!&quot;  :-)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="123" LastActivityDate="2012-01-12T08:22:47.357" />
  <row Id="60" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2012-01-12T09:23:39.673" Score="1" ViewCount="95" Body="&lt;p&gt;When I have asked friends this some have suggested that it is because transgendered males have an easier time blending in and looking like younger cis-males but I have heard about statistics that show that something like only 1/5 or 1/4 request for genital reconstruction surgery is by transgendered men.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Is there any accepted explanation for this?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="61" LastEditorUserId="140" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2012-01-12T22:56:20.023" LastActivityDate="2012-01-12T22:56:20.023" Title="How come there seems to be more female transgender people than male?" Tags="&lt;transgender&gt;&lt;genitals&gt;&lt;gender&gt;" AnswerCount="1" CommentCount="3" />
  <row Id="61" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="50" CreationDate="2012-01-12T09:32:53.497" Score="0" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;Small amounts of spermicidal is perfectly fine so I would probably suggest taking a quick wipe with a towel of the part being orally stimulated before if there is a noticeable coating, besides that you should of course not drink the stuff (if bought separate) or unroll and lick on a whole bunch of condoms in a row.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="61" LastActivityDate="2012-01-12T09:32:53.497" />
  <row Id="62" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="45" CreationDate="2012-01-12T09:51:11.487" Score="0" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Because a lot of people seemed pretty displeased with my earlier answer I'm rewriting it here:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I have a few speculations that I'm basing my theory on:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;There is a positive correlation between neurodiversity and and different kinds of fandom, as mentioned &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.tor.com/blogs/2009/08/neurodiversity-and-fandom&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;A larger diversity in gender identity, sexual orientation and sexuality is slightly more common among people within the spectrum as mentioned in &lt;a href=&quot;http://nominatissima.wordpress.com/2011/07/26/sex-the-spectrum-sex-positive-neurodiversity/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;this&lt;/a&gt; article.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Unfortunately this does not seem to be a very researched topic and my theory is mostly based on my experience from different forms of fandom and sex positive culture. My theory is as follows:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Neurodiversity is over-represented, compared to rest of society, in most kinds of fandom because it is often a culture where knowledge is higher valued than social skills. Along with neurodiversity and acceptance you get the higher number of HBT-persons in those fandoms. This I think is not special for furry fandom, what is special about furry fandom is that it is a fandom that is by a, not insignificant, number of the followers sexualized and people who accept one &quot;abnormal&quot; side of their sexuality is more likely to have several ways they diverge from the projected norm of society.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="61" LastEditorUserId="61" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2012-01-12T18:51:54.677" LastActivityDate="2012-01-12T18:51:54.677" CommentCount="5" />
  <row Id="63" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="19" CreationDate="2012-01-12T12:55:45.397" Score="1" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;Well, according to wikipedia, &lt;a href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Female_ejaculation#Nature_of_fluid&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;it's not urine&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Unfortunatly, mainly due to a poor scientific corpus, exact nature of emitted fluid is yet unknown.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="124" LastActivityDate="2012-01-12T12:55:45.397" CommentCount="2" />
  <row Id="64" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="52" CreationDate="2012-01-12T12:57:51.977" Score="5" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;According to &lt;a href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Erectile_dysfunction#Causes&quot;&gt;the wikipedia article&lt;/a&gt;, there are multiple possible causes. To name a few (order here is &lt;em&gt;not&lt;/em&gt; significant) :&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Drugs &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Neurogenic disorders&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Psychological causes&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Surgery&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Age/Aging&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Diseases&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Smoking&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="124" LastEditorUserId="13" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2012-01-12T16:46:26.253" LastActivityDate="2012-01-12T16:46:26.253" />
  <row Id="65" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="50" CreationDate="2012-01-12T13:14:47.293" Score="4" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;The most common spermicide is &lt;a href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Nonoxynol-9&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;nonoxynol-9&lt;/a&gt;, so I'll address that.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;According to the &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.lifestyles.com/condom-faqs/#qC17&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;Lifestyles Condom FAQs&lt;/a&gt;, which does not cite any sources, but comes from a reputable company:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;Neither the two lubricant bases, silicone and mono-propylene glycol, nor the spermicide nonoxynol-9 itself are harmful if ingested in the small amounts present on a condom.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;And according to the &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.cdc.gov/niosh/ipcsneng/neng1558.html&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;U.S. Centers for Disease Control and Prevention&lt;/a&gt;, which I would take as authoritative:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;Ingestion:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;  &#xA;  &lt;ul&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Acute Hazards/Symptoms: (none specified)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;Prevention: Do not eat, drink, or smoke during work.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;li&gt;First Aid / Fire Fighting: Rinse mouth.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If there are no hazards or symptoms, and the worst you have to do is rinse your mouth, I would take that to mean pretty conclusively that, in any quantity you would be likely to ingest incidentally, there's nothing to worry about.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="111" LastEditorUserId="111" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2012-01-12T13:38:59.703" LastActivityDate="2012-01-12T13:38:59.703" />
  <row Id="67" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="44" CreationDate="2012-01-12T13:41:25.213" Score="5" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;My understanding from reading a book*  on ESO (Extended Sexual Orgasm) is that orgasm and ejaculation are separate events, although they usually occur together.  You can separate them. I've experienced once or twice. However, if you're doing this for pleasure (why else ?) I'd recommend instead trying for an Extended Sexual Orgasm. It feels way better. Imagine a 5 minute orgasm. (Also I find orgasm without ejaculation much less pleasurable. Sort of like eating delicious food but not swallowing it.).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you'd like to work on having an ESO, here are a few tips.  (I will say this is much easier with a partner because the trick is to not get too aroused. So with a partner it's nice and intimate. With masturbation it gets boring (or you cross the point of no return. *Imagine a graph of your arousal level over time. Normally it rises sharply and you have an orgasm. But if you can go very very slowly the arousal rises slowly and everything, including the orgasm gets stretched out.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;*(I don't see it on Amazon, but there are many on &quot;ESO&quot;) &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="53" LastActivityDate="2012-01-12T13:41:25.213" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="68" PostTypeId="5" CreationDate="2012-01-12T13:53:22.723" Score="0" ViewCount="1" Body="&lt;p&gt;This tag is for questions relating to the psychological aspects of sexuality. This may include questions about both the causes and the effects of sexual activities, preferences, or other sex related areas.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="-1" LastEditorUserId="31" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2012-01-12T15:03:11.853" LastActivityDate="2012-01-12T15:03:11.853" />
  <row Id="69" PostTypeId="4" CreationDate="2012-01-12T13:53:22.723" Score="0" ViewCount="" Body="The psychological and mental aspects of sexuality" OwnerUserId="-1" LastEditorUserId="31" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2012-01-12T15:03:15.143" LastActivityDate="2012-01-12T15:03:15.143" />
  <row Id="70" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2012-01-12T16:36:16.303" Score="4" ViewCount="56" Body="&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What are the changes to the menstrual cycle caused by taking the emergency contraceptive pill?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;Is it possible for it to hasten the menstrual cycle?&lt;br&gt;&#xA;Are there any other important changes?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Edit&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To further make clearer this question:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A friend from my job told me once she had used a emergency contraceptive pill to prevent a pregnancy and  two days later her period happened (when it should have happened about 13 days later).&#xA;About a year later she went to the beach and remembering that it happened before took again such pill hoping to repeat such situation before going to her vacations in order to be more comfortable during her travel.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;And i would like to ask about the main changes to know if such situation is possible; but also i think that as part of this site it would be good to have it as an answer because sooner or later the &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&quot;contraceptive pill effects&quot;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; would appear as a question.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="136" LastEditorUserId="136" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2012-01-13T21:12:41.113" LastActivityDate="2012-01-15T15:38:07.440" ClosedDate="2012-01-16T21:41:02.113" Title="What effect does the emergency contraceptive pill have on the menstrual cycle?" Tags="&lt;menstrual-cycle&gt;&lt;contraceptives&gt;&lt;emergency-pill&gt;" AnswerCount="1" CommentCount="7" />
  <row Id="71" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="60" CreationDate="2012-01-12T17:13:05.587" Score="11" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;There is very, very, very little research available about transgender people. Statistics about transgenderism are very difficult to come by. In the United States, this is due in part to the fact that the census &lt;a href=&quot;http://transequality.org/Resources/Census0309.pdf&quot;&gt;does not specifically count trans people&lt;/a&gt;. I would be interested to discover where you got the 20-25% statistic you cite in your question. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It's also important to remember that not all trans people seek sex reassignment surgery. Statistics about sex reassignment surgery do not accurately mirror statistics about transgenderism in general. &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.timesunion.com/local/article/Transgender-Local-statistics-2342390.php&quot;&gt;This article&lt;/a&gt; contains some statistics that were collected from a medical center in Albany. Note that only 31% of transwomen and 64% of transmen (in this particular, very limited, very poorly documented, very not-to-be-trusted survey sample) sought any form of surgery, including procedures for both primary and secondary sex characteristics.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.transgenderlaw.org/resources/transfactsheet.pdf&quot;&gt;This fact sheet&lt;/a&gt; cites resources from the late 90s, but it states that &quot;Over time, the gap between the reported numbers of&#xA;MTFs and FTMs transsexuals is closing&quot;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;(Sidebar: Though they are used in the fact sheet above, the terms &lt;code&gt;MTF&lt;/code&gt; and &lt;code&gt;FTM&lt;/code&gt; are descriptors for trans people that are outdated and disrespectful. &lt;code&gt;MAAB&lt;/code&gt; and &lt;code&gt;FAAB&lt;/code&gt; [Male or Female Assigned At Birth] are preferable; see &lt;a href=&quot;http://tranarchism.com/2010/11/26/not-your-moms-trans-101/&quot;&gt;this article&lt;/a&gt; for details on why.)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The lack of available research makes it difficult to answer your question adequately, but this might help. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="15" LastEditorUserId="15" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2012-01-12T18:07:49.227" LastActivityDate="2012-01-12T18:07:49.227" CommentCount="6" />
  <row Id="73" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="34" CreationDate="2012-01-12T19:57:21.480" Score="17" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The tl;dr version:&lt;/strong&gt; every woman is different. If you have / could have access to multiple partners or female friends who aren't particularly shy, feel free to ask them what their reactions constitute. Otherwise, this is something that you and your partner should communicate about, as it will lead to a more positive experience for &lt;em&gt;both of you&lt;/em&gt; long term. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As you mentioned, there are a &lt;em&gt;lot&lt;/em&gt; of potential responses in women to indicate an orgasm. There are also a number of factors that can affect the visibility and &quot;obviousness&quot; of these responses as well. I'll do my best to be thorough. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The most common response (that is also difficult to &quot;fake,&quot; if that's what you're asking) is the flexing and the extension of the pelvic floor muscles. Women who regularly perform &lt;a href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Kegel_exercise&quot;&gt;Kegel exercises&lt;/a&gt; will have longer and more intense orgasms, and their Kegel muscles will flex more rapidly and with more strength. Duration of an orgasm is affected by how much foreplay over what kind of time, as well:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Q: My orgasms seem too short. Is there a way to make them last longer?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;  &#xA;  &lt;p&gt;A: According to our experts, yes. Try doing some trusty Kegels, those pelvic-floor exercises that work the muscles that control your urine flow. “A few times a day, do both long holds for 10 to 20 seconds and short rhythmic squeezes—as many as you can to give your orgasm more comic-book pow!” say Miller and Solot. A longer buildup to climax can help make yours last longer too. “Rather than rushing from zero to 60,” say Miller and Solot, “get yourself close, then back off a bit. You can repeat this 10 times if you have the patience! By building up the tension, you earn yourself a bigger release.”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;(Above from &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.glamour.com/sex-love-life/2008/04/orgasm-questions#ixzz1jGWW5rko&quot;&gt;Glamour Magazine&lt;/a&gt;.)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The flexing of pelvic floor muscles is probably the most universal reaction. Partners can feel this either, if they are male, around the shaft of the penis or around fingers during manual stimulation. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Since an &lt;a href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Orgasm&quot;&gt;orgasm&lt;/a&gt; results in the release of &lt;a href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Oxytocin&quot;&gt;oxytocin&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Prolactin&quot;&gt;prolactin&lt;/a&gt;, a lot of women will sigh deeply following an orgasm, and their entire bodies will relax fully. Many women experience hypersensitivity in the &lt;a href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Refractory_period_%28sex%29&quot;&gt;refractory period&lt;/a&gt; following an orgasm, which is a common response to overstimulation. Basically, this feels like every nerve ending is tingling, all over one's body. In this period, stimluating the clitoris is actually actively uncomfortable, however maintaining firm pressure on the clitoris can extend the orgasm further and prepare the body for a next iteration. If she does maintain a hypersensitivity period, running a hand along legs, her torso, across and under (eg. where the wire of her bra would run) her breasts, inside forearms (especially if she spends lots of time at a keyboard!) and at the juncture of her neck and collarbone will be stimulating without being overwhelming.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A number of women will have a number of muscles tense or spasm in the buildup to an orgasm. Most common are legs bending at the knees (some women will do this to help angle their partner further into the vagina) or toes curling. Depending on how aroused and how intense the oncoming orgasm is, her back may arch as well. This may be combined with a full body shudder or undulation, the latter of which will basically be her back arching and continuing into her rolling her hips. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Other have mentioned other fairly common physical reactions, including but not limited to:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Flushed skin (especially about the sternum and breasts, face, and neck)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Erect nipples&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Darkened areolae (usually tied with flushed skin)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Goosebumps&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Elevated heart rate&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Increased respiration&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Sudden vaginal excretion (originating from the &lt;a href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Bartholin_glands&quot;&gt;Bartholin glands&lt;/a&gt;, as well as the cervix)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Swelled vulva&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;However, a number of these indicate arousal as much as orgasm. Furthermore, depending on the amount of exertion that she has engaged in during intercourse, as well as if she's having multiple orgasms, these could be signs of strenouous physical activity. A full, complete list of female phyiscal response during orgasm is meticulously documented in Chapter 15: Physiology of Sexual Response and Orgasm of Alfred Kinsey's &lt;a href=&quot;http://books.google.com/books?id=9GpBB61LV14C&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Sexual Behavior in the Human Female&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Notably, women who are relaxed about engaging in sexual intercourse are most likely to experience orgasm:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;Many women believe they should have an orgasm—or better yet, several—every time they have sex. But if you're too busy chasing or counting them, you'll miss out on all of the pleasurable sensations in between. I had one patient who'd never had an orgasm and had spent years trying. But when she learned to relax and just enjoy the sensations she did experience, guess what happened? She climaxed.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;(From &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.glamour.com/sex-love-life/2006/07/orgasms#ixzz1jH22BNU2&quot;&gt;Glamour Magazine&lt;/a&gt;.)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Furthermore, while the clitoris is a cluster of nerve endings, the most concentrated &quot;knot&quot; of nerves is located slightly above and to the left of the clitoris itself. To use a metaphor, if one were to overlay a clock centered on the clitoris, this &quot;knot&quot; is located roughly between 10 o'clock and 11 o'clock. Stimulation of this during foreplay and/or intercourse can yield a stronger reaction in the female partner. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Also, because the clitoris is a cluster of nerves, other avenues can be used to prolong, stimulate, intensify, or extend an orgasm. Many women like the feeling of pressure on her &lt;em&gt;mons&lt;/em&gt; along with clitoral stimulation, as the nerve runs up through the &lt;em&gt;mons&lt;/em&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Questions about how vocal a female partner will be about. This, as with everything else, is entirely dependent on the partner herself. Some women &lt;a href=&quot;http://tvtropes.org/pmwiki/pmwiki.php/Main/TheImmodestOrgasm&quot;&gt;react very vocally&lt;/a&gt; and, ah, with gusto. However, &lt;a href=&quot;http://tvtropes.org/pmwiki/pmwiki.php/Main/TheModestOrgasm&quot;&gt;most women are quieter&lt;/a&gt;, either due to socialization (many cultures impose an ideal of women being quiet and submissive in all aspects) or just by nature. (I'd like to point out that the &lt;a href=&quot;http://tvtropes.org/pmwiki/pmwiki.php/Main/TheGruntingOrgasm&quot;&gt;same variation occurs in men&lt;/a&gt;; some are louder throughout the experience, some quieter but communicative physically, etc.) Generally speaking, the release of oxytocin and prolactin will yield a very deep sigh or groan accompanied by a total body relaxtion, almost to the point of her turning into a deadweight. (And, if your partner &lt;em&gt;is&lt;/em&gt; loud, perhaps consider &lt;a href=&quot;http://xkcd.com/316/&quot;&gt;taking advantage of it&lt;/a&gt;.)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Ultimately, if you aren't sure if your partner is having an orgasm, suggest she masturbate in front of you. This will offer multiple benefits: &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You'll learn what she likes.&lt;/strong&gt; When engaging in autoeroticism, she'll touch herself in ways that (presumably) bring her the most pleasure. Gauge how much pressure she likes, how much clitorial stimulation, if she strokes her vulva, breasts, inner thighs, etc. &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Voyeurism is often a turn-on.&lt;/strong&gt; Encouraging your partner to masturbate in front of you might encourage her to come out of her shell more, if she's shy or circumspect, or even simply less experienced. Many people have a voyeurism/exhibitionist fetish that they either don't know about or haven't had the opportunity to act on. You could use the opportunity to mix in other play (self-denial, mutual masturbation, having the observing party bound and unable to particpate, etc) into the experience.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You'll be able to observe her orgasm.&lt;/strong&gt; Perhaps most important, you'll be able to observe her physical reaction to orgasm, from arousal to afterglow. You can observe how she reacts as she approaches orgasm, what she does to extend the sensation, and observe how sensitive she is following. &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Of course, offer to masturbate for your female partner, as well, especially if she's less experienced or a newer partner.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Finally, as a point of interest, the &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.guardian.co.uk/science/2011/nov/14/female-orgasm-recorded-brain-scans&quot;&gt;Guardian reported recently&lt;/a&gt; that the female orgasm had been captured in a series of brain scans.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="13" LastActivityDate="2012-01-12T19:57:21.480" CommentCount="2" />
  <row Id="74" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2012-01-12T20:29:30.283" Score="10" ViewCount="89" Body="&lt;p&gt;When I was 34 years old, I was single and life circumstances led me to realize several outstanding issues, including  sexual freedom. I carried all kind of sexual situations with absolute freedom, feeling fulfilled.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Now, I have been living with a woman and our two children for the last 5 years. I'm a loyal person and I don't like to cheat or lie, but I can't avoid the impulse to give free rein to my sexual needs with other women, or the feeling that I want to free myself in this way.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The question is: is possible to channel sexual desire into something else in order to mitigate this need and anxiety? Or can libido and sexual desire only be channeled through sex?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="82" LastEditorUserId="15" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2012-01-12T20:42:45.977" LastActivityDate="2012-01-16T10:46:06.073" Title="Is possible to channel sexual desire into something else other than sex?" Tags="&lt;psychology&gt;&lt;sexual&gt;" AnswerCount="4" CommentCount="3" />
  <row Id="75" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="74" CreationDate="2012-01-12T20:54:53.727" Score="4" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;You could channel your sexual desire into masturbation. It might help but ultimately you will still want to have sex with other people. There isn't a magic bullet to stop you wanting the things you want.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There is no reason why loving one person and having sex with other people are mutually exclusive. Plenty of people have healthy happy open relationships. Its not cheating if you have your partners permission.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="48" LastActivityDate="2012-01-12T20:54:53.727" CommentCount="2" />
  <row Id="76" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="5" CreationDate="2012-01-12T21:03:08.990" Score="1" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;Wikipedia has both a diagram and a description on its &lt;a href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/G-Spot&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;G-Spot article&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The general guideline is to insert one or two fingers into the vagina, with the pads of your fingers towards the pubic bone. Bend your fingers slightly and make a &quot;come hither&quot; type motion. The G-spot is normally about half an inch to an inch wide, roughly circular, and has a distinct texture.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As noted in the above Wikipedia article, and plenty of other places, there's a lot of disagreement about whether the G-spot exists. I can only advocate trying and seeing if it works for you!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="140" LastActivityDate="2012-01-12T21:03:08.990" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="77" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="5" CreationDate="2012-01-12T21:16:16.203" Score="0" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;The G-spot is located on the front wall of the vagina about a half to one finger-length inside. Easiest way to reach it is being face to face and sticking a finger inside the vagina making a come-hither motion with your finger, when the person is very aroused it will be a small area that feels rough or bumpy and have a slight spongy feel to it. What stimulation is appreciated varies and it is in no way a magical button for all persons with vaginas. Regardless of what Wikipedia says all medical professionals I've personally spoken to agree that it exists.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="61" LastActivityDate="2012-01-12T21:16:16.203" />
  <row Id="78" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="45" CreationDate="2012-01-12T21:19:17.620" Score="7" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;The same question cold be asked for musical fans or people who go to the ballet. Nothing in these activities causes homosexuality however either by culture or by nature these activities mainly appeal to homosexuals. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A large factor is culture. Straight men feel cultural pressure to act in a manly way. The quintessential furry activities such as snuggling, dressing up ect don't fit well with that image. The gay community as a whole is also much more accepting and open to fetishes. As such the fear of people finding out is less for homosexuals and the bar for entry is much lower.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I'm afraid I can only speak from experience as a gay furry. I don't know of any studies.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="48" LastActivityDate="2012-01-12T21:19:17.620" />
  <row Id="79" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="74" CreationDate="2012-01-12T21:25:09.570" Score="11" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;While Tom's answer is certainly right and masturbation can definitely be a way to go here, as can nonmonogamy, if that's not what you're getting at, then maybe re-channeling your sexual desire into a creative outlet is a possibility. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Sublimation, as it's called, often gets a bad rap and I don't know that there are any conclusive indications of whether it's 100 percent effective in the long term, but it's not an uncommon way for many people to deal with undesirable emotions or urges. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For example, if you're angry you might take it out on an inanimate object; no one gets hurt and in the end you might feel at least a little better. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Same principle with sexual urges. You can try re-directing those desires towards something creative or constructive (not that sex can't fall into those categories, but you know what I mean).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;However it seems as if you're talking about persistent urges and sometimes there is no easy fix for those. If monogamy is non-negotiable in your relationship it may just be something you have to come to terms with. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="104" LastEditorUserId="15" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2012-01-12T22:53:33.757" LastActivityDate="2012-01-12T22:53:33.757" CommentCount="6" />
  <row Id="80" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="4" CreationDate="2012-01-12T21:43:54.003" Score="4" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;The biggest risk from TENS units is from current crossing the heart. That can induce a heart attack, with obvious potentially lethal consequences.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Some of the risk will vary depending on the power of the TENS unit you're using. A low power unit has much lower risk of doing any damage than a high power one; if you're just buying a cheap off-the-shelf unit, it's not going to be very high power. That doesn't mean you can be reckless with it, however.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The common guideline I've heard is the one you mention: nothing above the waist. That said, the leaflet that came with my TENS machine recommended a variety of pad positions on the back for treating certain kinds of back pain; I assume this still has a low risk provided you don't also attach contacts to the front of the torso. The rules for &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.kink.com/k/shooting_rules.jsp&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;Kink.com shoots&lt;/a&gt; additionally allow &quot;Nipple Clamps where the nipple completes the circuit (electricity passes on through the nipple, not from breast to breast or breast to other area of the body)&quot;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Another rule I've not seen repeated very often but makes sense to me is to avoid using two people to complete a circuit, for example don't have one contact near the penis and the other near the vagina for vaginal intercourse: unless you're otherwise covered in rubber, there's a risk you could, for example, touch your partner's face or torso, and suddenly there's a path for current to travel across both partners' hearts.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Wikipedia has &lt;a href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Transcutaneous_electrical_nerve_stimulation#Safety&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;some more safety guidelines&lt;/a&gt;, which I'd summarize as keeping contacts away from the head and the spine.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="140" LastActivityDate="2012-01-12T21:43:54.003" />
  <row Id="81" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2012-01-12T22:01:16.367" Score="2" ViewCount="86" Body="&lt;p&gt;From a strictly medical/psychological standpoint, how much masturbation is too much? At what point does it become harmful, either physically (e.g. for men, once you start chaffing?) or psychologically (e.g. if you're doing it more than five times a day, you might have an underlying issue that you're not dealing with), or physiologically (e.g. for men, you might permanently damage your sperm count)?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="39" LastEditorUserId="108" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2012-01-13T21:21:00.977" LastActivityDate="2012-01-14T01:01:41.460" Title="How much masturbation is too much?" Tags="&lt;masturbation&gt;" AnswerCount="2" CommentCount="3" />
  <row Id="82" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="81" CreationDate="2012-01-12T22:29:00.547" Score="7" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;At what point does it become harmful, either physically&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;That really depends on the person and how hard you're doing it. If you're doing it correctly then it should never become painful.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;or psychologically&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Again very subjective. If it starts to impact your social life or work/studies you need to reduce it. Otherwise go ahead.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;physiologically (e.g. for men, you might permanently damage your sperm count)?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There is no long term damage caused by masturbation (correctly done). There are lots of health benefits of masturbation including lower prostate cancer risk (see &lt;a href=&quot;http://sexuality.stackexchange.com/questions/25/medical-detriments-benefits-of-masturbation/32#32&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="48" LastEditorUserId="111" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2012-01-14T01:01:41.460" LastActivityDate="2012-01-14T01:01:41.460" />
  <row Id="83" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="81" CreationDate="2012-01-12T22:30:07.463" Score="7" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;I don't know that there's a medically accepted standard for &quot;too much&quot; masturbation. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I think it's safe to say that if you're experiencing any pain or discomfort from masturbation, as with any other activity, you should probably take it down a notch.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As far as psychologically, as long as the frequency of masturbation isn't making you uncomfortable, it's probably fine. There's no &quot;magic number&quot;. Obviously if you're just masturbating all day every day you may have a problem that you need to address, but if it's not precluding or negatively affecting important things in your life (family, friends, work, etc.) you're most likely all right. Of course if you're frequently feeling negative emotions connected to masturbation you might want to talk it over with a professional, regardless of how often you masturbate. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;One caveat: frequent masturbation, using a lot of friction, pressure, or speed (way more than you would get during sex with a partner) can cause what's called retarded ejaculation, which basically means that it becomes difficult or impossible to ejaculate from other kinds of stimulation.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;And no, you can't run out of sperm. Obviously you may ejaculate less after masturbating, but it's not a permanent issue. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="104" LastActivityDate="2012-01-12T22:30:07.463" CommentCount="5" />
  <row Id="84" PostTypeId="5" CreationDate="2012-01-12T23:37:05.933" Score="0" ViewCount="1" Body="" OwnerUserId="-1" LastEditorUserId="-1" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2012-01-12T23:37:05.933" LastActivityDate="2012-01-12T23:37:05.933" />
  <row Id="85" PostTypeId="4" CreationDate="2012-01-12T23:37:05.933" Score="0" ViewCount="" Body="Questions related to sexually transmitted diseases" OwnerUserId="-1" LastEditorUserId="61" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2012-01-12T23:47:30.877" LastActivityDate="2012-01-12T23:47:30.877" />
  <row Id="86" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2012-01-13T00:25:01.077" Score="6" ViewCount="31" Body="&lt;p&gt;The condom market is dominated by latex condoms. Is this because latex is more effective as a barrier for STDs and sperm than other materials? Or is it for some other reason, e.g. because latex condoms are the most cost-effective to produce?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;What is the most effective non-latex material for condoms, and how does it compare to latex?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="146" LastEditorUserId="15" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2012-01-13T01:15:58.253" LastActivityDate="2012-01-15T02:26:02.750" Title="How effective are non-latex condoms compared to latex condoms?" Tags="&lt;condom&gt;&lt;contraceptives&gt;&lt;safer-sex&gt;" AnswerCount="3" />
  <row Id="87" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="86" CreationDate="2012-01-13T00:42:42.390" Score="2" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;Lifestyles SKYN, non-latex condoms have been approved by the FDA to help prevent both Pregnancy and STDs according to &lt;a href=&quot;http://contraception.about.com/od/malecondom/g/SKYN.htm&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;this article&lt;/a&gt;. My conclusion: if the FDA approved it, I would imagine they're just as good as regular latex condoms at preventing STDs. While they are more expensive, they are also said to be more pleasurable to use than regular, latex condoms. SKYN condoms are made from polyisoprene, a relatively new material. This may also be why they're more expensive. The supply chain and costs of production haven't had time to flatten out like those for latex condoms have.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="39" LastActivityDate="2012-01-13T00:42:42.390" />
  <row Id="88" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="86" CreationDate="2012-01-13T01:50:49.943" Score="4" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;This depends very much on the material from which the condoms are made - &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.fda.gov/forconsumers/byaudience/forpatientadvocates/hivandaidsactivities/ucm126372.htm&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;The FDA has quite a bit to say&lt;/a&gt; about choosing the right kind of condom (and condom-compatible accoutrements like lubricants).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To summarize, most condoms are an effective barrier against sperm, but not all of them are effective against all diseases.  In particular, lambskin condoms (and presumably those made from any other kind of animal skin or membranes) may not be as effective in preventing the spread of sexually transmitted diseases, in particular viruses, which may be small enough to pass through the microscopic pores in the material.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The FDA's site recommends latex condoms, however other materials have also been shown to reduce the risk of sexually transmitted diseases (&lt;a href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Condom#Synthetic&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;polyurethane being the most common&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;br&gt;&#xA;For maximum safety look for a condom with a clear claim that it &lt;code&gt;reduces the risk of transmitting sexually transmitted infections&lt;/code&gt; printed on the packaging.  These claims are regulated by the FDA and manufacturers are required to test their condoms and provide supporting evidence in order to include it in their packaging/marketing materials.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="50" LastActivityDate="2012-01-13T01:50:49.943" />
  <row Id="89" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="97" CreationDate="2012-01-13T02:07:42.643" Score="4" ViewCount="62" Body="&lt;p&gt;This question is asked completely out of ignorance, I am fully willing to admit. But I would like to learn. In reading &lt;a href=&quot;http://sexuality.stackexchange.com/q/60/31&quot;&gt;this question&lt;/a&gt; and specifically &lt;a href=&quot;http://sexuality.stackexchange.com/a/71/31&quot;&gt;the answer by Abby&lt;/a&gt;, it links to a fact sheet that has a simple table. Within the table is the following:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.stack.imgur.com/bIDy3.png&quot; alt=&quot;Fact Sheet Chart&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In the fact sheet, under sexual orientation, it lists two for MAAB (Hetero and Bi), and four for FAAB (Hetero, Bi, Gay, and Lesbian). But this is what confuses me. My best guess is that it is what the person identified themselves as being, but I would have thought that a FAAB transgendered individual would classify themselves as male, and therefore be gay, and not lesbian.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Which leads me to my (ignorant) question: When a transgendered person classifies themselves as heterosexual, does this mean that they would be attracted to the opposite gender of their gender at birth (I think it might be referred to in the article as 'natal' gender?) or the gender they identify themselves as? Or is that not necessarily something that is standard, so to speak, amongst the transgendered community?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Edit:&lt;/em&gt; Edited the terms to be more appropriate. Sorry, I didn't mean to offend anyone, I am just, as I said, ignorant but learning.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="31" LastEditorUserId="157" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2012-01-15T03:23:35.130" LastActivityDate="2012-01-15T03:23:35.130" Title="Does a Hetero MAAB Transgender mean they are attracted to men or to women?" Tags="&lt;transgender&gt;&lt;heterosexuality&gt;" AnswerCount="1" CommentCount="4" />
  <row Id="90" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2012-01-13T02:11:14.700" Score="2" ViewCount="20" Body="&lt;p&gt;Synthetic condoms such as Lifestyles SKYN or Trojan Supra are a great option for people with latex allergies seeking to practice safer sex.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Are there other advantages to these newer synthetic condoms, such as improved sensation or the ability to carry one in your wallet (which has been shown to degrade and weaken latex condoms)?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="50" LastActivityDate="2012-01-13T02:33:52.413" Title="What are some benefits of synthetic (non-latex) condoms?" Tags="&lt;condom&gt;" AnswerCount="1" />
  <row Id="91" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="86" CreationDate="2012-01-13T02:15:51.383" Score="4" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;TL;DR:&lt;/strong&gt; Use latex when you can, use synthetic when you &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.lifestyles.com/products/skyn/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;must&lt;/a&gt;. Avoid separate non-water-based lubricants.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Latex condoms are known for their elastic properties, its tensile strength exceeds 30 MPa and may be stretched to 800% before breaking (from Wikipedia which references &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/12264044&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;this PubMed article&lt;/a&gt;. There are even &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/viewer?a=v&amp;amp;q=cache:6N527TCAVD4J:211.67.52.20:8088/xitong/BZ%255C9429065.pdf+&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;pid=bl&amp;amp;srcid=ADGEESim74fVBDeWAPIWTFd_2ngNUTYyQPKMB3ab7nGOyMJhOEvejgoOwVTFxJoJGYaSubhSa8yW-UUnaPU1US03QQw9R6o5FvKAiZGVeMRb6QJ3UTyobrI3EzQEfyPruvImR8kRFxMd&amp;amp;sig=AHIEtbSrmLZZze1juoVSZqSwNbxStfvssA&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;standardized ISO requirements and test methods&lt;/a&gt; to ensure that every latex condom meets the minimum necessary to be effective. They test latex condoms for holes with an electrical current, only packaging it when it passes. In addition, a portion of each batch of condoms is tested for water leak and air burst.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;However, Latex condoms can be affected by &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.walnet.org/csis/med_research/oilstudy.html&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;certain types of lubricants&lt;/a&gt; that affect the latex. Also note that some people are also allergic for Latex and thus can't use these type of condoms, although synthetic latex condoms exist to work around these issues. An example condom is &lt;a href=&quot;http://condomunity.com/polyisoprene-skyn-lifestyles-condoms/2008/11/21/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;SKYN&lt;/a&gt;, which is known well to be useful for those with allergy; another reason &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.lifestyles.com/products/skyn/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;listed by their site&lt;/a&gt; is that it goes for better sensitivity. It however does not list anything about the effectiveness.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A comparison between latex and synthetic rubbers been made and listed in a contraception report, if the Wayback Machine allows it you can read about it &lt;a href=&quot;http://web.archive.org/web/20060926035226/http://www.contraceptiononline.org/contrareport/article01.cfm?art=243&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;on this WayBack link&lt;/a&gt;. A lot of articles I found suddenly seem to lose their existance, either because the site is rewritten or the site ceased to exist. As the site is currently offline, I can't tell you the exact results. Although the link is being referred to as that non-Latex condoms are not affected by certain types of lubricants of which Latex condoms are affected.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The same report however tells us that that these condoms can be stretched less and are thus more likely to break. Here is a response that mentions how polyurethane condoms aren't strectchy, with the caveat that the difference is small if used properly:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;Polyurethane is a plastic and stronger than latex, but not quite as stretchy. For that reason, polyurethane condoms are slightly more likely to break or slip. However, this performance difference is small and does not have much of an effect on the condom's overall efficacy.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;  &#xA;  &lt;p&gt;&amp;mdash; &lt;a href=&quot;http://goaskalice.columbia.edu/do-polyurethane-condoms-protect-well-against-stis-latex&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;Alice - Do polyurethane condoms protects well against STIs?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Polyisophrene condoms on the other hand, share the quality of latex and non-allergic condoms together.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So, as a conclusion latex gets the preference but you really shouldn't be worrying. You can however switch to synthetic condoms like SKYN when you really look for the need to have a more natural feeling or when you have an allergic problem. When using latex condoms, watch out with lubricants as they can affect the condom; this is not seen with synthetic condoms. The most important thing is proper use of the condom.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The FDA gives the following buying guide if you want to remain effecient:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;Use this handy shopping guide as a reminder of what to look for when buying condoms and lubricants.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;  &#xA;  &lt;p&gt;Be sure to choose:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;  &#xA;  &lt;p&gt;[X] Latex&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;  &#xA;  &lt;p&gt;[X] Disease prevention claim on package label&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;  &#xA;  &lt;p&gt;Also consider:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;  &#xA;  &lt;p&gt;[ &amp;nbsp;] With lubricant&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;  &#xA;  &lt;p&gt;[ &amp;nbsp;] Separate lubricant (Select only water-based lubricants made for this purpose.)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;  &#xA;  &lt;p&gt;&amp;mdash; &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.fda.gov/forconsumers/byaudience/forpatientadvocates/hivandaidsactivities/ucm126372.htm#shop&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;FDA shopping guide&lt;/a&gt;, for more summary from that page, check &lt;a href=&quot;http://sexuality.stackexchange.com/a/88/145&quot;&gt;voretaq7's answer&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="145" LastEditorUserId="145" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2012-01-15T02:26:02.750" LastActivityDate="2012-01-15T02:26:02.750" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="92" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="90" CreationDate="2012-01-13T02:33:52.413" Score="1" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;Synthetic condoms have the following properties:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Because the material is softer, it has a natural feel and allows for more heat transfer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Due to the more soft, natural, warmer feel; you get an enhancement in sensation as you &lt;em&gt;feel more&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The down side of these satisfying properties, is that they are &lt;a href=&quot;http://sexuality.stackexchange.com/a/91/145&quot;&gt;slightly less efficient than latex condoms&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="145" LastActivityDate="2012-01-13T02:33:52.413" CommentCount="4" />
  <row Id="93" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2012-01-13T02:52:08.000" Score="10" ViewCount="86" Body="&lt;p&gt;I don't mean immediately afterwards but within a short time frame. I'm referring to both males and females regarding this biological phenomenon. What causes it and why?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="141" LastEditorUserId="141" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2012-01-17T05:46:36.140" LastActivityDate="2012-01-18T09:59:10.427" Title="Why does ejaculation induce urination afterwards?" Tags="&lt;ejaculation&gt;&lt;urination&gt;" AnswerCount="3" CommentCount="2" FavoriteCount="1" />
  <row Id="94" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="56" CreationDate="2012-01-13T03:08:08.053" Score="6" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;TL;DR&lt;/strong&gt;: Given the right music, it has effect due to dopamine &amp;amp; off-set thoughts, not due to Testosterone.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;What effect does music have on us? How does it affect sex?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.msnbc.msn.com/id/40990339/ns/health-behavior/t/your-brain-music-enjoyable-sex/&quot;&gt;news article from the Associated Press, reformed by MSNBC&lt;/a&gt;; it is mentioned that Robert Zatorre and Valorie Salimpoor of the McGill University in Montreal wrote in the journal Nature Neuroscience that instrumental music produces a dopamine response. So, without even requiring voice, music will make you more satisfied. During sexual intercourse, this dopamine response thus results in extra enjoyment.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Another reason, besides dopamin, is that music helps you off-set your thoughts from thoughts that have a negative effect towards your relation; you don't want to be thinking about the problems in your life. Given the right choices that put your thoughts on the actual sexual intercourse, without being uncomfortable can surely help. Surely avoid the radio or your personal collection, but try romantic collection albums...&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Are there other related studies? Do they have effect?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;At the Nara University of Education in Japan, they have &lt;a href=&quot;http://chialvo.org/Curso/UNR2010/Modulo%201%20Musica%20Y%20Neurociencia/Publicaciones/FUKUI.pdf&quot;&gt;discovered a relation between Music and Testosterone levels&lt;/a&gt;. A group of students was asked to take a pause of 10 minutes and then listed to music in 30 minute intervals. After each interval, they captured the saliva to be used in the measurement. The notable result of this study is that the the testerone levels of males significantly decreased where-as the testerone levels of females significantly increased, remarkable is those that listened to silence had nearly the same testerone levels before and after. Some types had more influence compared to other types of music.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.stack.imgur.com/7AoR5.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.stack.imgur.com/xhli9.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sadly, while Testosterone affects development, it has &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Testosterone&quot;&gt;barely any&lt;/a&gt; physiological or sexual effects.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;But yet I mentioned because it is an interesting read none-the-less.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="145" LastActivityDate="2012-01-13T03:08:08.053" />
  <row Id="95" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="93" CreationDate="2012-01-13T03:26:43.903" Score="9" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;It depends on how full your bladder was before you start, as well as its size. The act of ejaculating involves some muscles that squeeze the bladder, this makes urine build up and gives you the feeling like you have to go urinate because your bladder was under pressure. Luckily, most men can't urinate during erection...&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="145" LastActivityDate="2012-01-13T03:26:43.903" CommentCount="4" />
  <row Id="96" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="5" CreationDate="2012-01-13T04:03:36.950" Score="6" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;h2&gt;Where does the female G-Spot lie?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;When inserting your finger(s), feeling upwards; you can feel a bulb around two inches in. On the image below, under the point (4) points to; you see a bulb which starts one inch in and stops around three inch in.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This is pretty common, here is &lt;a href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/G-Spot&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;what Wikipedia has to say&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;The G-Spot (4) is reportedly located one to three inches into the vagina, at the side of the urethra (6) and the urinary bladder (2).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;  &#xA;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.stack.imgur.com/rKhKz.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.askmen.com/dating/vanessa_100/115_love_secrets.html&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;This article&lt;/a&gt; describes how to find it:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;First of all, the G-spot is easiest to locate when a woman is sexually aroused, so don't stint on your foreplay first. (You knew I would get that in!)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;  &#xA;  &lt;p&gt;To locate and master the woman's G-spot, face your partner while she is lying on her back and insert your index or long middle finger into her vagina as far as it will easily go. Then crook it up toward yourself in a &quot;come hither&quot; motion, sliding your fingertip along the top of the vagina until you find an area that is rougher than the rest of that vaginal wall. (Make sure you have your fingernails clipped short and buffed before you do this -- sharp fingernails will definitely spoil the effort.) This rough or slightly ridged area is the &quot;G-spot,&quot; and touching it will often cause a woman to react with surprise or pleasure.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.askmen.com/dating/vanessa_100/115b_love_secrets.html&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;The second page&lt;/a&gt; shares some more love secrets, outside the scope of &lt;em&gt;finding&lt;/em&gt; the G-Spot.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Where does the male G-Spot lie?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;While everyone hears about the female G-Spot. Males have also something that is not medically called a G-Spot, but does actually result in very similar experiences like even being able to reach full body orgasms.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Guess what? It's the Prostate. Given the controversy, I leave &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.askmen.com/dating/vanessa/23_love_secrets.html&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;reading the details&lt;/a&gt; up to the reader. This was also mentioned in &lt;a href=&quot;http://sexuality.stackexchange.com/a/9/145&quot;&gt;this answer&lt;/a&gt;, the comments guide on locating it. It's very similar to the female G-spot...&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;And for those looking to be convinced, &lt;a href=&quot;http://sexuality.stackexchange.com/questions/7/why-is-anal-sex-pleasurable&quot;&gt;there is also this question&lt;/a&gt;. Your mileage may vary, though.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="145" LastEditorUserId="145" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2012-01-15T02:15:00.660" LastActivityDate="2012-01-15T02:15:00.660" />
  <row Id="97" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="89" CreationDate="2012-01-13T04:24:30.113" Score="8" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;Everyone is different. What one person might mean when they describe themselves using certain words will very likely differ from what another person means while using the same descriptors. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;That said, people who have undergone some or all of the process of transitioning between genders will generally describe themselves with words that refer to the gender they present - that is, the gender that is not necessarily the one they were assigned at birth. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For example: a heterosexual transman is a man who was assigned as female at birth who is romantically and/or sexually attracted to women; a gay transman is attracted to men. A gay transwoman is a lesbian; a heterosexual transwoman's attractions are to men. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There will always be exceptions to this rule, as with any rule, but I think it is a good place to start.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The table in your question has a cell indicating that 12% of transmen identify as lesbian. This goes against what I know of the trans community, but it could possibly be explained depending on when during the transition process the survey information was taken. Sometimes heterosexual transmen identify as lesbians before they transition. (Sometimes they don't. I cannot stress enough: everyone is different. No rule or statement will apply to everyone.)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;At any rate: I disagree with the information in the table, or at the very least I don't understand what they are getting at. In my experience it's very infrequent to find a transman who also identifies as a lesbian - the two identities are sort of at odds. (A person who identifies in both of these ways could possibly consider themself bigender or genderqueer. They could also consider themself a lesbian transman if that's what they felt.)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The long and the short of it is that there are no rules that govern who gets to use what words to describe themselves. It's always a matter of personal choice.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="15" LastActivityDate="2012-01-13T04:24:30.113" CommentCount="3" />
  <row Id="98" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2012-01-13T09:10:28.860" Score="15" ViewCount="87" Body="&lt;p&gt;Imagine the following situation: mom and dad are snuggling on the sofa. The kids are playing with toys in the same room. The parental snuggling escalates, and Mom ends up giving Dad a hand job. This would absolutely be taboo in my culture.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Obviously, it's taboo if this act of sexual expression &lt;strong&gt;includes&lt;/strong&gt; the kids (&quot;incest&quot;). Further, it's taboo if the act is a &lt;strong&gt;display, or performance&lt;/strong&gt; for the children as audience. I'm pretty sure that such taboos are universal across all human cultures.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;That's not what I'm asking about.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I'm asking about the situation where the adults are engaging in what would otherwise be a normal, acceptable sexual activity, with the exception that it is not explicitly hidden from the kids' view. This is taboo in my culture, but I wonder if that taboo is universal.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Are there any cultures where sexual acts are not actively concealed from children? Is there any information documenting why it is or is not acceptable to perform sexual acts in the presence of children?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="17" LastEditorUserId="43" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2012-01-16T20:45:02.097" LastActivityDate="2012-01-16T20:45:02.097" Title="Is it universal to conceal sexual expression from children?" Tags="&lt;taboo&gt;&lt;culture&gt;&lt;anthropology&gt;" AnswerCount="2" CommentCount="9" />
  <row Id="99" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="24" CreationDate="2012-01-13T16:30:26.313" Score="-1" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;Nope. You said yourself: the only technique which can't be performed is gliding the foreskin. But that can be replaced by any kind of moisturizer. It won't be the exact same but there is no pleasure lost as long as it's wet enough. In fact, even with the foreskin intact, it's often much better to do it with liquids anyway.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Other than that, there are ways to &lt;em&gt;masturbate&lt;/em&gt; in which &lt;a href=&quot;http://skeptics.stackexchange.com/a/1378&quot;&gt;circumcision&lt;/a&gt; brings no difference at all, such as hand pressing and pulsing the base, rubbing only the glans against something, not to mention if you have a partner...&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;And maybe it's good to remember ways in which even the penis doesn't play, such as body massage (yes, men can in fact ejaculate only from that), handling the testicles/scrotum, &lt;a href=&quot;http://sexuality.stackexchange.com/questions/7/why-is-anal-sex-pleasurable&quot;&gt;anal stimulation&lt;/a&gt;, etc.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="137" LastEditorUserId="50" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2012-01-14T22:18:01.823" LastActivityDate="2012-01-14T22:18:01.823" CommentCount="2" />
  <row Id="100" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2012-01-14T07:40:39.327" Score="6" ViewCount="60" Body="&lt;p&gt;I know that there are a potentially infinite number of fetishes out there, but I am curious to see if there are any studies that have been done to explore which fetishes are the most common, even if just within a target population. Especially if it explores potential differences between genders, ages, etc. Are there any studies that have looked at this?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="31" LastActivityDate="2012-01-15T23:06:07.893" Title="What fetishes are most common?" Tags="&lt;fetish&gt;" AnswerCount="2" CommentCount="4" />
  <row Id="101" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2012-01-14T09:01:40.883" Score="5" ViewCount="40" Body="&lt;p&gt;Alternate title: &quot;How did primitive people [control population/keep population stable]?&quot;, but this implies that they did it consciously, and that it was a matter of control. I don't want to make either of those assumptions.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We have a huge technological advantage for population control compared to primitive people. We have latex condoms, birth control pills, and an understanding of fertility that far surpasses what our distant ancestors had. According to &lt;em&gt;Sex at Dawn&lt;/em&gt;, primitive people may also have had more sex than modern people. I think they started having sex at an earlier age, but I don't have a reference. They had better nutrition than moderns, which should lead to increased fertility. According to they research of Price and Pottenger, they had easier births with fewer deaths.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In all these regards, they should have been producing a lot more babies than we make today. And yet, their populations didn't grow, while today we have 7 billion humans on the earth. Why?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Human_population&quot;&gt;Wikipedia says&lt;/a&gt; &quot;hunting and foraging, a lifestyle that by its nature ensured a low population density&quot;, but does not explain &lt;em&gt;how&lt;/em&gt; that happens. I am confident that starvation was not the mechanism, nor endless bloody warefare, nor short lifespans, regardless of Hobbes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Also, I recognize that &quot;primitive people&quot; actually describes an extremely diverse set of cultures, so there may not be a single answer.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;(By primitive, I mean pre-agricultural, so don't mix in the middle ages or anything!)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="17" LastActivityDate="2012-01-15T08:57:35.983" Title="How did populations of primitive people remain stable?" Tags="&lt;birth-control&gt;&lt;population&gt;&lt;anthropology&gt;" AnswerCount="1" CommentCount="4" FavoriteCount="1" />
  <row Id="102" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="104" CreationDate="2012-01-14T17:20:20.183" Score="3" ViewCount="48" Body="&lt;p&gt;Many people have concerns when regarding anal sex and its possible consequences. Be it infections, loosening of anal muscles and so forth.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;What are the possible side effects of having anal sex, and how probable they are?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="60" LastActivityDate="2012-01-15T22:57:40.027" Title="Are there any side effects to anal sex?" Tags="&lt;anal-sex&gt;&lt;side-effects&gt;&lt;problems&gt;&lt;penetration&gt;&lt;anus&gt;" AnswerCount="3" />
  <row Id="103" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="102" CreationDate="2012-01-14T17:39:42.277" Score="2" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;Anal muscles are the same as any other. The more you use them the stronger they get not weaker. Anal sex done correctly has no negative side effects. The scare stories about anal sex causing loosening are unsubstantiated.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It is worth noting howerver that there is a higher chance of STD transmission with anal sex compared to vaginal. Condoms are a must unless it's with a long term STD tested partner. (I would apply exactly the same advice to vaginal sex)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="48" LastEditorUserId="48" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2012-01-14T17:47:25.823" LastActivityDate="2012-01-14T17:47:25.823" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="104" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="102" CreationDate="2012-01-14T23:21:33.517" Score="5" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;Wikipedia covers health risks well (http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Anal_sex#Health_risks). &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;Anal sex can expose participants to two principal dangers: infections&#xA;  due to the high number of infectious microorganisms not found&#xA;  elsewhere on the body, and physical damage to the anus and the rectum&#xA;  due to their fragility.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Taking it slow, latex barriers (condoms), generous lube, and short, filed fingernails all help.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The sphincters are muscles. If you stretch them too fast they can get very sore. Again, take it slow and use plenty of lube.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;With a woman, use a condom in each orifice, and change condoms when changing play. If you engage in analingus (&quot;rimming&quot;), you are at risk of infection orally. A dental dam can work as a latex barrier here.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you're considering having anal sex, do more research. Good resources include Tristan Taormino's &lt;a href=&quot;http://rads.stackoverflow.com/amzn/click/1573442216&quot;&gt;book&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;http://rads.stackoverflow.com/amzn/click/B000V99H18&quot;&gt;video&lt;/a&gt;. Review these materials with your partner. Discuss concerns. Take it slow. Don't count on things going well the first time.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Unprotected anal sex between a man and a woman could still produce a pregnancy, although it's unlikely. Don't count it as a way to enjoy sex without contraception.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A bowel movement after anal sex may be affected. Having time &amp;amp; access to a toilet and shower after sex is nice.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="17" LastActivityDate="2012-01-14T23:21:33.517" CommentCount="3" />
  <row Id="105" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2012-01-15T02:25:53.053" Score="4" ViewCount="58" Body="&lt;p&gt;It seems that, especially in popular media, men are more often portrayed as having particular sexual fetishes than women, so I'm just wondering if there's any truth to that notion in real life.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="104" LastEditorUserId="31" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2012-01-15T04:00:56.297" LastActivityDate="2012-01-16T20:44:49.287" Title="Are fetishes more common in men than in women?" Tags="&lt;fetish&gt;&lt;gender&gt;" AnswerCount="2" CommentCount="3" FavoriteCount="2" />
  <row Id="106" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="24" CreationDate="2012-01-15T03:42:47.370" Score="2" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;I can't answer this directly as I have been circumcised almost my entire life, but it's worth noting that circumcision became popular in the United States &lt;a href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/History_of_male_circumcision#Male_circumcision_to_prevent_masturbation&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;specifically to curb masturbation&lt;/a&gt; in boys:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;In the 19th century […] Both opponents and supporters of circumcision agreed that the&#xA;  significant role the foreskin played in sexual response was the main&#xA;  reason why it should be either left in place or removed.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A lot of people will tell you that there is no difference, but unless they were circumcised later in life and can actually compare based on experience, I wouldn't take it at face value as they could be rationalizing the procedure—nobody wants to admit they're in any way lacking in the sex department; &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.nocircpa.org/4642.html&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;misconceptions&lt;/a&gt; about it being &quot;just a flap of skin&quot; also support this. Physiologically, &lt;a href=&quot;http://people.howstuffworks.com/circumcision1.htm&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;the evidence&lt;/a&gt; points to a loss of sensation:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;Those nerves packed into the foreskin provide additional stimulation&#xA;  during sexual activities. Its lubricating function also assists in&#xA;  sexual intercourse. Additionally, the frenulum (which is removed in&#xA;  some circumcisions) provides stimulation. Since the glans is kept&#xA;  moist and soft by the foreskin, it too is more sensitive to touch.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Yes, gliding and moisture can be simulated, but you can't simulate the nerve bundles and blood cells that would otherwise reside there.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="155" LastActivityDate="2012-01-15T03:42:47.370" CommentCount="2" />
  <row Id="107" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2012-01-15T03:45:42.390" Score="3" ViewCount="42" Body="&lt;p&gt;Does frequent masturbation affect sex drive, in either direction? For example, does it make one less likely to desire sex with others because gratification is already being achieved? Or, conversely, does it habituate the body to regular gratification, thus increasing sex drive?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="157" LastEditorUserId="157" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2012-01-15T03:53:32.143" LastActivityDate="2012-01-15T21:01:48.377" Title="Does frequent masturbation have an effect on sex drive?" Tags="&lt;masturbation&gt;&lt;sex-drive&gt;" AnswerCount="2" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="108" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="101" CreationDate="2012-01-15T08:51:16.510" Score="6" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;This actually comes from a number of different factors. This digs a lot into anthropology though, and less on sexuality, but I'll try to be thorough in my answer and cite as many sources as possible. Since, however, it isn't very easy to get life expectancy data from the eras in which you are talking as it must be taken from skeletons and other such sources, it has to be extrapolated a little bit going backwards. So bear with me a little.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Maximum_sustainable_yield&quot;&gt;Maximum Sustainable Yield&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Maximum_sustainable_yield&quot;&gt;maximum sustainable yield&lt;/a&gt; (MSY) in terms of populations is the highest number of people that can be sustained given the available food and resources. This is observed not only in humans, but in all populations, and usually ends up looking like the following:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.stack.imgur.com/6S0Ku.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Maximum Sustainable Yield: Credit Wikipedia&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Image credit Wikipedia.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Now, this graph here is a very simplified theoretical graph, and, as we all know, they don't align properly to real life all the time. Now let's look at the human population graph.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.stack.imgur.com/gY2ho.gif&quot; alt=&quot;Human Population over time&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Image credit &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.geol.umd.edu/sgc/lectures/anthropocene.html&quot;&gt;University of Maryland Department of Geology&lt;/a&gt; (really)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This is the best chart I can find for human population. You'll notice that human population really leveled out there (essentially) for thousands of years. You didn't see that combinatorial growth until the industrial revolution. Minor bumps here and there, and you see increases 2000 BC and around 0 AD but the real growth you could expect is around the industrial revolution. That is when the MSY sky rocketed. Before this time you had minor inventions which certainly helped increase the MSY, but nothing like in the industrial revolution. At that point we were able to produce enough food, shelter and other necessities to be able to sustain livelihoods in a consistent manor. This is what has allowed the population to grow now, and what prevented it from growing before. More kids meant either you or they starve. Which did happen, frequently. And that leads us to...&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;Disease and Mortality&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Disease really starts to set in more later, but we'll cover it a bit. The industrial revolution helped &lt;a href=&quot;http://books.google.com/books?hl=en&amp;amp;lr=&amp;amp;id=eMBG_soDdNoC&amp;amp;oi=fnd&amp;amp;pg=PA1&amp;amp;dq=diseases%20industrial%20revolution&amp;amp;ots=t0IRdwIAvJ&amp;amp;sig=VPeS4Zxt7ZAXsYJG4DHlIVi_-OY#v=onepage&amp;amp;q=diseases%20industrial%20revolution&amp;amp;f=false&quot;&gt;spread diseases amongst people faster&lt;/a&gt; as people were now grouped together more closely. But one of the issues of being a hunter/gatherer society is needing to be on the move. And while on the move there are many things that can kill children very quickly. Animals, cold, getting lost, even eating the wrong berries. &lt;a href=&quot;http://books.google.com/books?id=1-HWKKKIhBQC&amp;amp;lpg=PA309&amp;amp;ots=zuaMEJt8YT&amp;amp;dq=hunter%20gatherer%20child%20rearing&amp;amp;lr&amp;amp;pg=PA313#v=onepage&amp;amp;q=hunter%20gatherer%20child%20rearing&amp;amp;f=false&quot;&gt;This ebook&lt;/a&gt;, though missing a few pages, seems to have some pretty good information about the topic. Including the following equation on page 313 pertaining to the survival chances of children in hunter/gather societies. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.stack.imgur.com/z3qiu.png&quot; alt=&quot;Equation for child survival rate&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This book focuses more on the sociological aspects of their survival, but that will play into this significantly as well.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Now for mortality and life expectancy. I was trying to not use Wikipedia as a reference if I could help it, but they actually have a really good chart on this &lt;a href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Life_expectancy#Life_expectancy_variation_over_time&quot;&gt;on the Life Expectancy article&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://i.stack.imgur.com/NlLSU.png&quot; alt=&quot;Life Expectancy Chart&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Chart Credit Wikipedia&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You'll notice that, as children, there is a higher mortality rate, as indicated often by the notes (once the get to 15, they are expect to live...). And while this chart takes into account childhood mortality rate, it does not take into account pre-natal mortality rate. With advances in modern medicine, giving birth has had a much higher success rate (&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.cdc.gov/nchs/data/nvsr/nvsr56/nvsr56_10.pdf&quot;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You'll notice in the chart, the Neolithic age has the lowest life expectancy of any other age. And this, mostly, is the age in which you are discussing. Many children born never reached sexual maturity and therefore could never produce offspring. This meant that the population never grew exponentially as you might expect if each of two or three children would have two or three children.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h2&gt;tl;dr&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In my research for this, I did stumble across a paper that seemed to be talking directly to what your question gets at, and is actually where some of the data for the life expectancy chart comes from. &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.brown.edu/Departments/Economics/Papers/2007/2007-14_paper.pdf&quot;&gt;The Neolithic Revolution and Contemporary Variations in Life&#xA;Expectancy&lt;/a&gt; by Oded Galor and Omer Moav seems to answer your question (a little side-ways since their focus is on life expectancy, but still). Specifically, on page 5, footnote 12, it says:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;As is well established in the evolutionary biology literature since&#xA;  the seminal work of Lack [1954], the allocation of resources between&#xA;  offspring ‘caring’ and ‘bearing’ is subjected to evolutionary changes.&#xA;  Lack (1954) suggests that clutch sizes (e.g., number of eggs per&#xA;  nest), among owls and other predatory vole-eating birds, for instance,&#xA;  are positively related to food abundance. He argues that the clutch&#xA;  size is selected such that under any feeding conditions fertility&#xA;  rates ensure the maximal reproductive success. Furthermore, Cody&#xA;  [1966] documents the existence of significant differences between&#xA;  clutch sizes of the same bird species on islands and nearby mainland&#xA;  localities of the same latitude. In temperate regions where food is&#xA;  more abundant in the mainland than on islands, the average clutch size&#xA;  is smaller on the islands. For instance, Cyanoramphus novaezelandeae,&#xA;  the average mainland clutch is 6.5 whereas the average in the island&#xA;  is 4.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Which is basically what I was discussing with the MSY above. I didn't get a chance to read through all of it yet, but the parts I did read seem to discuss their points with a fair bit of depth. At the very least, I've got it bookmarked for myself for later.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So, in short, it wasn't necessarily about how much sex they were having and their fertility, but more about how long they could survive and how many people could be sustained which contributed to a somewhat stable population number.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="31" LastEditorUserId="31" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2012-01-15T08:57:35.983" LastActivityDate="2012-01-15T08:57:35.983" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="109" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="115" CreationDate="2012-01-15T11:12:26.763" Score="-1" ViewCount="60" Body="&lt;p&gt;I've been with women who I could tell shaved hair off their nipples.  Apart from being mildly  amusing, is this normal?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="97" LastEditorUserId="15" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2012-01-16T03:43:54.280" LastActivityDate="2012-01-16T03:43:54.280" ClosedDate="2012-01-16T21:20:29.960" Title="Is it normal for women to have hair on their nipples?" Tags="&lt;nipples&gt;&lt;hair&gt;&lt;breasts&gt;" AnswerCount="1" CommentCount="4" />
  <row Id="110" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="74" CreationDate="2012-01-15T13:19:12.627" Score="-2" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;First the short answer, talk with your partner.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Now, the long answer...&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Adding to the answer of @Tom and @bird, masturbation can also become an nightmare if it gets out of control, because you will &quot;think&quot; (in reality your not, as this is one of you can run, but can't hide) that your hiding something, and become addicted in that feeling...&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So, the best answer might be, tell the truth to your partener, be open about what you fell, so that both of you can find a solution you (as in you and her) may even realize that something is not so perfect in your relationship and find ways to improve it.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="168" LastActivityDate="2012-01-15T13:19:12.627" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="111" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="100" CreationDate="2012-01-15T13:41:55.977" Score="2" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;According to this article in &lt;a href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Foot_fetishism&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;wikipedia&lt;/a&gt;, feet fetish is the most common fetish. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As a sidenote remember that fetishism is still considered an taboo theme in current society, so studies in this area tend to be only available as part of thesis or academic papers in psychology. And some kinds of fetishism, may also be not covered in any study, so the data available might not be faithful to reality.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="168" LastActivityDate="2012-01-15T13:41:55.977" CommentCount="3" />
  <row Id="112" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="56" CreationDate="2012-01-15T14:23:40.147" Score="0" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;What I think of it is that music being a sound wave, can intereact with your own brain cycles and induce some types of behavior, so in a sense it can influence sex. What I also think is that some types of music can induce a more seductive state than others, regardless of the country of culture. But there are also some types of music specific to some culture. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Jazz for example, happens to be in the general case, particularly smooth jazz. Obviously one can argue, that some tunes of deep or funky house do the same.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="168" LastActivityDate="2012-01-15T14:23:40.147" />
  <row Id="113" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="107" CreationDate="2012-01-15T14:50:41.543" Score="-2" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;I think that it habituates the body and decreases sex drive, in the sense that you are unlikely to try to have other types of sexual relation, because masturbation already does that for you.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="168" LastActivityDate="2012-01-15T14:50:41.543" CommentCount="2" />
  <row Id="114" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="98" CreationDate="2012-01-15T15:22:53.020" Score="1" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;This can have multiple views, so I will start by analyzing the pros and cons of each, and what could happen if their are put to extremes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hide from children&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This side, arguments that exposing children to sex is a negligence of parenting, because children should be protected. So the advantages of this:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;You can control when your children start to make those types of questions;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Your children will probably be less obsessed with it and are unlikely to go to some paths that you deem as bad;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;You will always look pristine to your children (in the sense that if they learn anything it will not be from you, whether this is bad or not is other question);&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;You will prevent your children from telling something that you do not want them to tell to others (it's horrible when someone knows about your sex life, because of what your children told them).&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Now the disadvantages of this:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;It will be much harder to protect your children, if they are contacted by a pedophile, since they will fell that they cannot tell anyone about what is happening to them;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Your children will still learn about it, but from some other source, and it might not be what you are expecting;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Your children might start to view you as a straighten parent, and talk to others about they doubts (if this is good or not depends of you, but you may start hearing rumors from other neighbors or friends about the questions your children make...)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Your children may still want to try it (in this case is like they say, the forbidden fruit is always the most wanted).&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Do not hide from children&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This side, arguments that sex being a human feeling should be treated as such (and draws a lot from naturism). So the advantages:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;You will not hide anything from your children;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Your children will see they parents as exactly how they are;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;You will avoid some questions (like where does babies come from?);&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;And the disadvantages:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Your children might see you as different from other parents, and create a shelf between the children they are to you and the children they are to others;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Your children might start to tell to others what they know, and neighbors might start to look differently at you;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Your children may considerer the topic to be normal stuff, and drag others to it (particularly the ones that look for the forbidden fruit);&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Your children may start to explore some things that might not be so good for them, or they may be more receptive to pedos.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Conclusion&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The conclusion of this is that it depends of what you think of it, and most parents are realizing that a middle ground between those two extremes (one where parents are available to answer questions in a objective way while not exposing their love life) is ideal, and that it is enough to keep them from doing something dangerous while getting them to stay informed about it.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As a final side note, like all things, children may think differently from their parents, so that a children raised on a traditional family may grow to be a more modern adult, and a adult raised on a more &quot;untraditional&quot; family may grow to be a more traditional adult.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="168" LastActivityDate="2012-01-15T15:22:53.020" CommentCount="4" />
  <row Id="115" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="109" CreationDate="2012-01-15T15:24:55.137" Score="5" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;Short answer: Yes. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Longer answer: On humans, hair grows everywhere except the soles of the feet, the palms of the hands, on the lips and on eyelids.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Androgenic hair (ie the thick hair that is common on male chests) may or may not be present on women, depending largely on genetic disposition and hormones (so in particular drugs like the contraceptive pill may make a difference). In general, it won't be as thick as on men, as one of the primary triggers for it growing is testosterone and related hormones, but it's presence, even in fairly large quantities, is certainly not abnormal.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As ever, if it causes problems, or rapidly changes, a trip to your doctor may be a good idea.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="140" LastEditorUserId="140" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2012-01-15T23:00:02.207" LastActivityDate="2012-01-15T23:00:02.207" />
  <row Id="116" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="70" CreationDate="2012-01-15T15:38:07.440" Score="0" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;The emergency contraceptive pill works by massively overdosing the body's hormone balance to try to induce a period and thus preventing a fertilized egg from implanting in the uterus.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;While this does induce a period, because of the massive hormone load the emergency pill contains, I'd personally think taking it just to induce a period is a Bad Idea; a better plan would be to run two packs of the regular contraceptive pill together to avoid a period entirely, or look at other options for preventing a period such as hormonal injections. These will be far less disruptive to the body's normal hormone balance.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;(Disclaimer: I am not a doctor, talking to your doc is probably a Good Idea.)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="140" LastActivityDate="2012-01-15T15:38:07.440" />
  <row Id="117" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="121" CreationDate="2012-01-15T16:14:00.927" Score="4" ViewCount="44" Body="&lt;p&gt;The start-stop technique relies on squeezing or putting pressure on the head of the penis to stop or delay the ejaculation. Does this pressure harm the sensitivity of one's penis in the long run?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="170" LastEditorUserId="175" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2012-01-16T03:43:48.820" LastActivityDate="2012-01-16T03:43:48.820" Title="Is the Start-Stop technique harmful in the long run?" Tags="&lt;masturbation&gt;&lt;physiology&gt;" AnswerCount="1" />
  <row Id="118" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="24" CreationDate="2012-01-15T16:40:39.680" Score="0" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;I've been circumcised when I was 20 years old, so I can tell you that I had the experience of masturbation with and without the frenulum. &#xA;As Hugh said you lose some sensation because of the lack of nerves in frenulum, noneless the core of sensation is in the penis head so you won't feel numb at all. &#xA;The &quot;gliding&quot; depends also of how elastic is your skin, some people need lubrication because it's hard to glide when your skin tends to be tight. In my case, I don't feel of needing lubrication or feeling numbness at all. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="172" LastActivityDate="2012-01-15T16:40:39.680" />
  <row Id="119" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="33" CreationDate="2012-01-15T19:00:18.593" Score="1" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;Sigmund Freud thought that children played with there food because they were thinking about playing with feces and that just about everything reminds everyone of a penis, probably according to Freud a square is just mans way of representing a short wide penis. Freud also thought that everyone had a kinky sexual thing going on with there mother so seemingly Freud does demonstrate projection by example.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Science is important. Psychology, study of the mind, is important. Sigmund is not.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Make sure you read at least a little about this topic elsewhere.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="174" LastActivityDate="2012-01-15T19:00:18.593" />
  <row Id="120" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2012-01-15T19:56:52.900" Score="-5" ViewCount="60" Body="&lt;p&gt;Take an example man and woman who are equally physically attractive.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The chances are that it's much harder for the man to find a sexual partner than for the woman.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Some sexual behaviours such as sexual dominance, sexual crime and porn are considerably more male associated than female. &lt;strong&gt;How much is this due to the inequality of availability between the genders?&lt;/strong&gt;  &lt;strong&gt;By constrast, how much is it due to, for example, built in evolutionary factors such as hormonal differences?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;That is the question, however this also displays itself in more subtle situations.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In some cases older men are attracted to younger, cute, more vulnerable women and this seems the way round that things occur. As opposed to older women taking advantage of younger men, for one it dosn't seem predatory or like taking advantage even if the woman chose a man who she thought wasn't getting any anywhere else. This sort of out of charecter behaviour would tend to be in cases where as women get older they no longer think of themselves as being desirable. In other words both men and womman who havn't been able to find a sexual partner for many years behave in the same way.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A similar dynamic could be at work regarding porn. I don't think men to whom woman similarly attractive as themselves are available, even if this were only occasionally, would view much porn.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Because to those not involved in them these things don't seem real and people involved don't seem relevent, so the issues are hard to improve. Sexual crime is really bad and whats more it shouldn't be necessary. In England we have a &quot;newspaper&quot; that shows a mostly naked womman each week one page in. I'm not sugesting that just having a paper that showed an attractive naked man one page in would fix things, but something thinking along those lines.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;When Google used to auto-correct &quot;she invented&quot; to &quot;he invented&quot;, nobody was sexist at Google, it was the internet they index.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="174" LastEditorUserId="13" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2012-01-16T20:45:45.153" LastActivityDate="2012-01-16T20:45:45.153" ClosedDate="2012-01-16T19:38:05.707" Title="sexual attitudes vs availability" Tags="&lt;men&gt;&lt;psychology&gt;&lt;crime&gt;&lt;woman&gt;&lt;society&gt;" CommentCount="12" FavoriteCount="1" />
  <row Id="121" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="117" CreationDate="2012-01-15T20:41:42.210" Score="4" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;No - penises are actually more durable than people think. Unless you are actually compressing it in a mechanical vice for extended periods of time you are unlikely to do any sort of damage to your sensitivity with your own hand.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There are theories that huge quantities (and I mean HUGE) can lead to decreased &quot;sensitivity&quot;, but that's more likely to be getting bored with your own attentions.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="176" LastActivityDate="2012-01-15T20:41:42.210" CommentCount="2" />
  <row Id="122" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="107" CreationDate="2012-01-15T21:01:48.377" Score="2" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;Ooookay,&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Short answer: it depends on the person.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Long answer: well, if that's what floats your boat and you don't &lt;em&gt;want&lt;/em&gt; anything else beyond just the orgasm - and let's face it sex is about more than that - then maybe. Gratification has all sorts of different forms and flavours, orgasm is only a tiny slice of the pie.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This is never going to be a cut and dried issue. Mechanically I don't think that lots of masturbation makes your overall sex drive (rather than your need for an orgasm RIGHT NOW) greater or smaller, I imagine that sex drive is simply what it is. Probably more influenced by other factors such as health or overall sense of personal well-being.   &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;TBH, I've always been a one or two orgasm a day girl and that hasn't really altered depending on whether I've got partners or not. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="176" LastActivityDate="2012-01-15T21:01:48.377" />
  <row Id="123" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="105" CreationDate="2012-01-15T21:29:43.763" Score="0" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;There is the theory of &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.hawaii.edu/hivandaids/Gender_and_Erotic_Plasticity__Sociocultural_Influences_on_the_Sex_Drive.pdf&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;sexual plasticity&lt;/a&gt; (also &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/10825779&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;this&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;http://books.google.se/books?id=c-HWugTvbDAC&amp;amp;pg=PA354&amp;amp;lpg=PA354&amp;amp;dq=erotic+plasticity+goats&amp;amp;source=bl&amp;amp;ots=oJaXbsyUr7&amp;amp;sig=Ew4MzaRRxOPHV0gY5vBz7FJ6PGA&amp;amp;hl=en&amp;amp;sa=X&amp;amp;ei=ukQTT5rRJcSB4gS47eGEBA&amp;amp;ved=0CDIQ6AEwAw#v=onepage&amp;amp;q=erotic%20plasticity%20goats&amp;amp;f=false&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;this&lt;/a&gt;) which essentially says that women are more likely to form, and continually reform, their sexuality based on their surroundings. Conversely, the theory holds that men's sexuality pretty much is set during childhood and stays pretty fixed. The book &lt;a href=&quot;http://rads.stackoverflow.com/amzn/click/0061707805&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;Sex at Dawn&lt;/a&gt; mentions stories of men having lost their ability to produce testosterone, which basically causes them to stop exhibiting aberrant sexual behavior and fetishes. The book has an example involving animals which could be aligned to this theory.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This theory has a lot of criticism and shouldn't be taken as confirmed truth in any way.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="61" LastEditorUserId="15" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2012-01-16T20:44:49.287" LastActivityDate="2012-01-16T20:44:49.287" />
  <row Id="124" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="105" CreationDate="2012-01-15T22:43:36.487" Score="-2" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;From my experience, perverts are a fairly even split of genders - in fact amongst the younger london scene there are more women than men and certainly women tend to be more open to try more things, especially in terms of same-sex partners. Generally the men I've come into contact with can often be worried about perceptions of &quot;being gay&quot; with respect to a number of sexual kinks, including pegging and anal fisting.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There are reasons for why men and women might have different outward attitudes to kink, and this is all very broad brush strokes, ultimately each person comes to kink / BDSM through a series of happenstances which are very much a product of their lives - it's very hard to generalise! &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It's also difficult to know whether one has a kink until one knows it exists. You need to see or (better) experience something in order to know  whether you like it or not. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;But, if we must, here are some broad brush strokes for you:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Women are brought up to be more sexually aware and more aware of themselves as sexualised beings (for good or for ill). For example, Ann Summers - UK high street sex shop - caters for women rather than men, the sex shops that do exist for men tend to be the more &quot;secretive&quot; and seedy porn outlets. The more open and overt a sex shop for men, the more likely it is to be for the gay market. Because women are more comfortable with their sexuality they are more likely to experiment.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;On the flip side, men are socially conditioned to &quot;take the lead&quot; and be more dominant - whether they are sexually dominant or not, which is another question for another time - so may seek out or initiate new types of sex in order to maintain this appearance. There is evidence that men buy more porn than women (possibly because there is more porn made for men than for women, so it's all a bit academic) and porn has increasingly shown more &quot;extreme&quot; and kinky types of sex, so men are likely to be aware of, and perhaps interest in trying it out. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="176" LastActivityDate="2012-01-15T22:43:36.487" CommentCount="6" />
  <row Id="125" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="102" CreationDate="2012-01-15T22:57:40.027" Score="0" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;Remember that some anal lubricant can be oil based which will degrade condoms. You can buy &quot;extra safe&quot; condoms which are good for anal sex, they tend to be thicker and have more lubricant.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Dildoes, plugs, fingers and lots of lube (I know folk have said it, but it's worth saying again. Lube! LUBE!) and - in the case of female partners - vaginal sex beforehand all help with the preparation and make the sex more enjoyable, as can a pillow underneath the hips to get the angle right.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It's worth thinking about the non-physical side effects too - obviously gain active consent, but be aware that anal sex, as with any new sexual practice might make you feel a bit more &quot;droppy&quot; than usual. In my experience this is especially true for boys on their first time as it can be a very intense sensation - you may need to ask to stop, have a rest, a cup of tea and a nice chat. Reminding your partner to breathe is also important, to avoid unwanted clenching. It's a powerful sensation, there are a lot of nerve endings there.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The point about using a new condom when moving from anal to vaginal play holds true for toys, fingers and anything else you intend to put inside someone - having some anti-bacterial wipes to hand is useful.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="176" LastActivityDate="2012-01-15T22:57:40.027" />
  <row Id="126" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="100" CreationDate="2012-01-15T23:06:07.893" Score="3" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;The top twenty fetishes on Fetlife - a posting board for perverts with many thousands of kinky members lists:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Bondage      &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Oral Sex      &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Spanking       &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Hair Pulling       &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Anal Sex       &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Blindfolds       &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Biting       &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Collar and Lead/Leash       &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Discipline       &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Handcuffs         &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Talking Dirty        &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Candle Wax         &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Lingerie         &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Masturbation         &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Master/Slave         &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Toys       &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Ass Play         &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Erotic Photography         &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Breast/Nipple Torture      &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Dildos&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Now, bear in mind that &quot;fetish&quot; is often conflated with &quot;stuff I'm into&quot; rather than the traditional meaning of the word whereby a generally considered non-sexual thing is fetishised into having sexual value.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="176" LastActivityDate="2012-01-15T23:06:07.893" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="127" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="19" CreationDate="2012-01-15T23:57:28.860" Score="5" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;According to an author of &lt;a href=&quot;http://rads.stackoverflow.com/amzn/click/089793380X&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;a book on female orgasms&lt;/a&gt;, it's similar to male ejaculate, except of course without sperm:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;&quot;Female ejaculate, like male ejaculate, is prostatic fluid, mixed with some glucose and trace amounts of urine, minus the sperm,&quot; says Deborah Sundahl, author of Female Ejaculation and the G-Spot: Not Your Mother's Orgasm Book! (Hunter House Publishers).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Quote taken from &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.thestranger.com/seattle/SavageLove?oid=17205&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;a Savage Love column&lt;/a&gt; on the subject. As far as I can tell, Sundahl's work is substantially more authoritative than Wikipedia at this point.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As for function, I don't know, but I'd keep in mind that there doesn't have to be an answer; it could simply be mirroring male physiology. (Why do men have nipples?)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="112" LastEditorUserId="112" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2012-01-16T01:11:56.757" LastActivityDate="2012-01-16T01:11:56.757" />
  <row Id="128" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="44" CreationDate="2012-01-16T01:50:03.227" Score="1" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;In my experience, the refractory period can be significantly shortened (for a male) by cutting off the flow of the ejaculation and minimizing its volume. This can be done by either squeezing the base of the penis, or by putting pressure on the perineum (just behind the scrotum), or by tensing the Kegel muscles.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This way the refractory period may be shortened to just a couple of minutes, or sometimes be eliminated altogether.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="171" LastActivityDate="2012-01-16T01:50:03.227" />
  <row Id="129" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2012-01-16T02:37:07.300" Score="3" ViewCount="42" Body="&lt;p&gt;I've heard it said that when hormonal contraceptive pills were originally developed/tested they suppressed the monthly bleeding completely, but that the test subjects didn't like this, and the sugar pills were added to cause a monthly &quot;artificial bleeding&quot;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This leads me to ask:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Does the menstrual fluid of a woman on the pill contain the same stuff as the menstrual fluid of a woman who is not taking contraceptives?&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;How safe would it be to always skip past the sugar pills, and thereby never have to experience menstrual bleeding again?&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;And, finally, is there something to the above story?&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="171" LastEditorUserId="171" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2012-01-18T14:48:59.650" LastActivityDate="2012-01-18T14:48:59.650" Title="Is it possible to avoid menstrual bleeding with hormonal birth control pills?" Tags="&lt;birth-control&gt;&lt;menstrual-cycle&gt;&lt;women&gt;" AnswerCount="2" CommentCount="9" />
  <row Id="130" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="129" CreationDate="2012-01-16T08:34:20.597" Score="2" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;Skipping the placebo pills and immediately beginning the next month's pills is likely to prevent menstruation. If this is done continuously, one using this method may experience spotting or breakthrough menstruation eventually. As for the safety of such a method, it's generally considered safe for most women for short-term use, however, none of this general information constitutes medical advice. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I myself have postponed or skipped one and sometimes two menstrual periods by skipping the last few pills of a blister pack, with no noticeable ill effect. At the time I was using Ortho Tri-Cyclen and was in my early twenties. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Articles on PubMed that deal with this topic:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Gold MA, Duffy K. Extended cycling or continuous use of hormonal&#xA;contraceptives for female adolescents. Curr Opin Obstet Gynecol.&#xA;2009 Oct;21(5):407-11. Review. PubMed PMID: &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/19528798&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;19528798&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Kuhl H, Birkhäuser M, Mueck A, Neulen J, Thaler C, Kiesel L,&#xA;Braendle W. [Long-cycle treatment in oral contraception]. Ther&#xA;Umsch. 2009 Feb;66(2):101-8. Review. German. PubMed PMID: &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/19180430&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;19180430&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Hitchcock CL. Elements of the menstrual suppression debate. Health&#xA;Care Women  Int. 2008 Aug;29(7):702-19. Review. PubMed PMID:&#xA;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/18663630&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;18663630&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="175" LastEditorUserId="175" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2012-01-16T19:33:01.690" LastActivityDate="2012-01-16T19:33:01.690" CommentCount="3" />
  <row Id="131" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="25" CreationDate="2012-01-16T08:42:22.720" Score="1" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;Add to that list of benefits that it can relieve symptoms of Restless Leg Syndrome.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Marin LF, Felicio AC, Prado GF. Sexual intercourse and masturbation: potential&#xA;relief factors for restless legs syndrome? Sleep Med. 2011 Apr;12(4):422. Epub&#xA;2011 Mar 4. PubMed PMID: 21377419.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="175" LastActivityDate="2012-01-16T08:42:22.720" />
  <row Id="132" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="74" CreationDate="2012-01-16T10:46:06.073" Score="-2" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;I can also agree about the communication part. It is absolutely crucial in a relationship no matter the topic/problem.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;My ex is channelling her sexual frustration into creative processes like painting or writing.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="181" LastActivityDate="2012-01-16T10:46:06.073" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="133" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2012-01-16T12:04:04.057" Score="4" ViewCount="27" Body="&lt;p&gt;Are there any reversible contraceptive treatments commercially available for men? (E.g. a male version of the pill, or the implant?)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This seems to have been the topic of quite a lot of interest (the &lt;a href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Male_contraceptive&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;Wikipedia page on Male Contraceptives&lt;/a&gt; cites that &lt;em&gt;hemp seeds&lt;/em&gt; was used for this purpose as early as 40 CE) and the same page lists a number of &quot;Methods in Development&quot; -- yet there seems to be &lt;em&gt;no&lt;/em&gt; products or treatments commercially available anywhere.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Tell me I'm missing something.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="171" LastActivityDate="2012-01-16T12:22:51.963" Title="What contraceptive treatments are there available for men?" Tags="&lt;birth-control&gt;&lt;male&gt;" AnswerCount="1" CommentCount="1" FavoriteCount="1" />
  <row Id="134" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="129" CreationDate="2012-01-16T12:20:29.410" Score="1" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;My gynecologist tells me there's no reason skipping periods would be harmful, though the more you skip the more likely breakthrough bleeding is to occur. She recommended skipping the &quot;rest period&quot; between rings (I use the NuvaRing rather than the pill) for women who have significantly uncomfortable periods. The literature I was given from the clinic indicates this is common advice in the field, as well. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="157" LastActivityDate="2012-01-16T12:20:29.410" CommentCount="4" />
  <row Id="135" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="133" CreationDate="2012-01-16T12:22:51.963" Score="1" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;The literature I picked up from Planned Parenthood suggests that only physical methods are available at this time for male temporary birth control, such as condoms, withdrawl, and &quot;outercourse&quot;. &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.plannedparenthood.org/health-topics/mens-sexual-health/birth-control-men-22600.htm&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;Web source&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="157" LastActivityDate="2012-01-16T12:22:51.963" />
  <row Id="137" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="98" CreationDate="2012-01-16T20:15:13.750" Score="6" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;The short answer: No, it is not universal to &quot;conceal&quot; sexual expression from children. In some cultures, the physical realities of the living space more or less prevent that from being possible.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;However&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;, &quot;not concealing&quot; is different from &quot;flaunting&quot; or &quot;not even trying to hide&quot;. As an anthropologist by training, the best example I can think of off the top of my head is from the book &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://rads.stackoverflow.com/amzn/click/0674004329&quot;&gt;Nisa: The Life and Words of a !Kung Woman&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; by Marjorie Shostak. &lt;a href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Marjorie_Shostak&quot;&gt;Shosta&lt;/a&gt;k is a well-known, well-respect American anthropologist who did a lot of ethnographic research on the &lt;a href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/!Kung_San&quot;&gt;!Kung&lt;/a&gt; people of Africa's Kalahari Desert. She interviewed !Kung women about many, many things, including sex and sexuality:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;Miraculously, it seemed, Bau talked freely about things I had wanted to hear, but hadn't, until then. We talked seven times over a period of two weeks; I took notes on all that I understood. She explained how children eventually became aware of their parents' sexual intercourse - &lt;strong&gt;conducted discreetly at night in the same one-room hut&lt;/strong&gt;. That was how children got their ideas for sexual play. At first they played that way with friends and sometimes even with their brothers or sisters. As they grew older, they stopped playing with their siblings and played only with children of the opposite sex. She herself had played &quot;house&quot; when she was a child, and she remembered a time when two playmates had been discovered having &quot;sex&quot; under the blankets.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;(from Nisa introduction, p. 17, emphasis mine).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;As with all anthropology, this is not infallible evidence. Shostak herself notes:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;  &lt;p&gt;Winning Bau's trust had been the first step; trying to understand what her confidences meant came next. I knew enough not to assume that what she told me was necessarily true. Informants often told anthropologists what they thought they wanted to hear. Some even told outright lies - from concealment, from indifference, or just for amusement. It was also possible that the way Bau talked was governed by cultural forms I didn't know, but which she assumed I understood.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;(ibid.)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;But Bau's stories, coupled with other interviews, the abundant free time children have and her own observations about the type of play that !Kung children engage in, led Shostak to believe that the believe that much of this process of sexual discovery are true for most !Kung people.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Methodological difficulties aside, this points to the conclusion that yes, there are some cultures where sex isn't totally hidden from children. Adults can be discreet about it, but it is assumed a natural part of a child's development that he or she will notice sexual acts being conducted by their parents. Arranging private meetings in which to engage in sexual acts is not very easy, so they try to be as discreet as can and don't seem to worry much about what they can't really control (e.g., a child pretending to be asleep but secretly watching).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This is just one example that I recalled off the top of my head; there may be others, but one example is enough to dispel any claim of &quot;universality.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;(Note: The above quotes come from the introduction; there's actually a whole chapter called &quot;Discovering Sex&quot; that's worth a read.)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="43" LastEditorUserId="43" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2012-01-16T20:30:10.653" LastActivityDate="2012-01-16T20:30:10.653" />
  <row Id="138" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="25" CreationDate="2012-01-17T00:39:31.167" Score="0" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;From a psychological view, this depends whether or not it becomes frequent or something you can control or not.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you can not control it, then it becomes a &lt;a href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Sexual_addiction&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;sexual addition&lt;/a&gt;, and as such the detriments are:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Lower self-esteem;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Isolation;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;...&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Also, this &lt;a href=&quot;http://allpsych.com/journal/sexaddiction.html&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;article&lt;/a&gt;, this &lt;a href=&quot;http://psychcentral.com/lib/2006/what-is-sexual-addiction/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;one&lt;/a&gt; and this &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.medicinenet.com/sexual_addiction/article.htm&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;one&lt;/a&gt; have a lot more of detriments...&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If it is not a addition, then by being a sexual activity, the brain releases dopamine, which causes a feeling of satisfaction and pleasure, associated with sex and as such it may make one more happy, but just because it is a sexual activity (this is a very powerful but, because any kind of sexual activity causes the same thing)&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.reuniting.info/science/sex_in_the_brain&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;This link has more info&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;And that's the view on the psychological side of it.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="168" LastActivityDate="2012-01-17T00:39:31.167" />
  <row Id="139" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2012-01-17T02:44:21.190" Score="0" ViewCount="30" Body="&lt;p&gt;Why is Christianity sex-restrictive? I don’t mean the reasons as portrayed in the religion’s canon, but rather, from a socioeconomic or historical perspective, how does/did the Christian church benefit from controlling the place, time, and ways in which humans explore or talk about sexuality?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="155" LastEditorUserId="155" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2012-01-17T07:11:46.253" LastActivityDate="2012-01-17T07:11:46.253" ClosedDate="2012-01-17T15:23:11.373" Title="Why does Christianity seek to restrict or control sexual activity and discourse?" Tags="&lt;religion&gt;" CommentCount="7" />
  <row Id="140" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2012-01-17T06:58:08.163" Score="0" ViewCount="27" Body="&lt;p&gt;Even when used perfectly, oral contraceptives are not completely effective. (&lt;a href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Combined_oral_contraceptive_pill#Effectiveness&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;Wikipedia's article&lt;/a&gt; says the failure rate is 0.3%.) Though the normal menstrual cycle is simulated, the hormonal cycle is presumably very different while on the pill; does this mean that failures do not tend to follow the normal fertility cycle? Is it completely impossible to combine any sort of calendar-based method with the pill?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="112" LastActivityDate="2012-01-19T15:05:39.377" Title="Fertility while on the pill" Tags="&lt;birth-control&gt;&lt;contraceptives&gt;" AnswerCount="1" CommentCount="2" />
  <row Id="141" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2012-01-17T07:08:49.067" Score="2" ViewCount="18" Body="&lt;p&gt;It's possible to find failure rates for essentially all birth control methods (Wikipedia has a nice &lt;a href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Comparison_of_birth_control_methods#Effectiveness_of_various_methods&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;comparison page&lt;/a&gt;). They're defined as the probability of pregnancy during the first year of use. Sources generally seem to say that the probability is for &quot;typical&quot; couples. What does that mean? Is it actually just a mean or median over the sample? Are there any good resources which include some indication of amount of sexual activity corresponding to the given failure rate, so that couples can better know their &lt;em&gt;actual&lt;/em&gt; risk?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="112" LastActivityDate="2012-01-17T07:08:49.067" Title="Measurement of birth control effectiveness" Tags="&lt;birth-control&gt;" CommentCount="3" />
  <row Id="142" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="145" CreationDate="2012-01-17T07:38:21.653" Score="5" ViewCount="50" Body="&lt;p&gt;Why is “dangerous” sex—be it because of being in public, cheating on a partner, not using birth control, because their parents would disapprove, or any other subversive act with potentially undesirable consequences—a turn-on for some people? If, evolutionarily speaking, sex is a means to procreation and therefore survival, why is a sense of danger, which we would otherwise instinctually avoid, something that people would be drawn to rather than repelled by in that kind of a situation?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="155" LastActivityDate="2012-01-20T12:52:47.330" Title="Why does a sense of danger often heighten sexual pleasure?" Tags="&lt;fetish&gt;" AnswerCount="3" CommentCount="2" FavoriteCount="1" />
  <row Id="143" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="93" CreationDate="2012-01-18T02:01:21.477" Score="1" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;In females, urination shortly following coitus can prevent urinary infections by flushing away any foreign substances or bacteria that may have been introduced into the area by sexual activity. For that reason it's a commonly encouraged practice in folk wisdom as a measure against &quot;honeymoon syndrome&quot; aka cystitis.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="175" LastActivityDate="2012-01-18T02:01:21.477" />
  <row Id="144" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="93" CreationDate="2012-01-18T09:59:10.427" Score="2" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;When it comes to men, it is a way for the body to clean out the sperms that wasn't ejected in to the female. So it is perfectly natural to need to urinate after sex.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="181" LastActivityDate="2012-01-18T09:59:10.427" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="145" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="142" CreationDate="2012-01-18T10:08:31.770" Score="0" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;It's kind of similar like that they say that &quot;rules are made to be broken&quot;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Let's say you are bankrupt, out of money, and really desire to eat or have something that you really like. For some people this gives a high desire to go steal, while they could actually spent time instead on trying to get yourself some work. But well, that would make them wait for their money.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Acts like these are also dangerous, you don't want to get caught and have the undesirable consequence to land up in jail. If you are able to do the act without getting caught, you have some kind of enjoyment like &quot;Yeah, I was able to get myself X for free and nobody saw it.&quot; While this is not the best instinctual example, this shows why one would do it anyway despite the sense of danger to achieve what he wants right now.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In other words, no cookie did ever taste as good as the one you'd have covertly slipped from a cookie jar.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Consider &quot;repetitive sex in the bedroom&quot; versus &quot;different sex in various places in various ways&quot;...&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="145" LastActivityDate="2012-01-18T10:08:31.770" />
  <row Id="146" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2012-01-18T18:57:13.280" Score="0" ViewCount="45" Body="&lt;p&gt;The world has come a long way since the &quot;rhythm method&quot;, and while artificial birth control (ABC &amp;mdash; includes drugs, barriers, and IUDs) is far more common, there are a good number of people who practice natural family planning (NFP), a practice which is rooted in periodic abstinence instead of introducing some external ABC. Many of these claim to be over 97% effective. (Some claim parity with ABC techniques).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I have heard of an NFP technique which was simple, highly effective, and would be incredibly accurate immediately (as opposed to a month of charting as with Billings). Does such a thing exist? (And what is a good resource on it?)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="103" LastEditorUserId="103" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2012-01-23T14:41:53.067" LastActivityDate="2012-01-23T14:41:53.067" Title="What is a simple alternative to ABC?" Tags="&lt;birth-control&gt;" CommentCount="7" />
  <row Id="147" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="140" CreationDate="2012-01-19T15:05:39.377" Score="-1" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;No, as I understand it; women menstruate after their hormonal level crashes.  The pill simulates this hormonal crash by fooling the woman's body during the first 3 weeks of the cycle to think it is pregnant (Progesterone?), and then during the period week, the hormone goes away and frequently the week off pill is either just sugarpill, or is an iron supplement (since people get a bit anaemic during times of heavy bleeding).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="83" LastActivityDate="2012-01-19T15:05:39.377" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="148" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="142" CreationDate="2012-01-19T21:18:05.433" Score="1" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;There could be a mixture of factors.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;One being that not everyone likes and furthermore many would be put off by danger in sexual situations, so this dosn't apply to them.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Also, along the same lines, some engage in risky behavior for other reasons that are not related to the risk, for example having an affair because they want to try another sexual partner without informing their current one, the danger in this case may still be a turn off.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Another is the excitement of doing something forbidden, which may be related to sex such as kinky, dangerous sexual play or not related, but for some heighten sexual pleasure, such as cheating or being on top of a tall building.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Some like dangerous situations in general, dangerous sex being merely another dangerous situation.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Also is that one could associate sex with danger, expecting one to come with the other, finding it easier to feel both at once or even just having one remind them of the other. They may have no experience of sexual situations without danger. Especially given its forbidden, secret, seedy or animalistic qualities, a need to be misleading or behave differently, association with recreational drugs such as alcohol, the physical and emotional dangers and drains, social pressure, the futile sense of worthlessness and depression of unending failure, confusing mixtures of emotions, light headedness or inabilty or think properly, the unknown or unfamiliar, social consequences and pressures including others opinions and finally risks such as rejection, embarrassment, miscommunication, being made a fool or taken advantage of, depict, the other person abruptly becoming worried, legal consequences and pregnancy this could entail.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="174" LastEditorUserId="174" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2012-01-19T21:57:36.417" LastActivityDate="2012-01-19T21:57:36.417" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="149" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2012-01-20T00:43:27.970" Score="0" ViewCount="29" Body="&lt;p&gt;How is it possible to handle more than one partner in a good way? &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Both in a sexual encounter together with three or mote people and when you have more than one sexual encounter but not in the same time.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="181" LastActivityDate="2012-01-20T13:14:49.390" Title="How is it possible to handle more than one partner in a good way?" Tags="&lt;polysexuality&gt;&lt;multiple-partner&gt;" AnswerCount="1" CommentCount="3" />
  <row Id="150" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2012-01-20T06:16:12.100" Score="0" ViewCount="14" Body="&lt;p&gt;Before a couple decides to fluid bond, they may decide to get tested for a variety of sexually transmitted diseases. It would be nice to be able to show a &quot;clean bill of health&quot;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;However, I read that blood tests don't detect genital herpes reliably. What other STDs have this limitation?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="17" LastActivityDate="2012-01-21T00:23:50.470" Title="Which STDs can't be reliably detected in a blood test?" Tags="&lt;std&gt;&lt;testing&gt;" AnswerCount="1" />
  <row Id="151" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2012-01-20T06:43:08.750" Score="0" ViewCount="10" Body="&lt;p&gt;I've seen advice not to bother with certain STD tests if you're not in a risk group, or if you haven't observed certain symptoms. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Getting a &quot;clean bill of health&quot; sounds reassuring, even if you're not in a risk group. What tests should that include?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;HIV seems like an obvious one, for example.  &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="17" LastActivityDate="2012-01-20T12:34:20.803" Title="Which STD tests should people get before fluid bonding?" Tags="&lt;std&gt;&lt;testing&gt;" AnswerCount="1" />
  <row Id="152" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="151" CreationDate="2012-01-20T12:34:20.803" Score="1" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;Most decent STD clinics will test you for everything.&#xA;If in doubt, ask them what services they provide.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you are in the UK, NHS direct are good people to call - &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.nhsdirect.nhs.uk/&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;http://www.nhsdirect.nhs.uk/&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;If anyone has the equivalents for other countries and can post below, that would be great.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The key thing is about &lt;em&gt;when&lt;/em&gt; you get tested, some STDs have an incubation period, so you might need a couple of tests over a period of time.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Remember - tell them the truth about your sexual history.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I would also recommend getting a heptatitis vaccine, especially if you are going to engage in heavy play involving cutting etc.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="176" LastActivityDate="2012-01-20T12:34:20.803" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="153" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="149" CreationDate="2012-01-20T12:50:06.253" Score="5" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;OK, I'm going to try and cover this, but it is quite a broad question.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;GOLDEN RULES&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Honesty - Say what you are looking for, don't offer more than you can give&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Self Awareness - Know yourself, your limits, orientation and whether you really, really want this. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Communicate - Talk to all partners invovled, preferably together, so everyone is clear on what is going on. Give your expectations up front and LISTEN to what other people are saying.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Think - Don't let the idea of Hot Threesomes cloud your judgement. Take time to decide whether this is the best thing for you, for your partner and for the other people involved. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Plan - How and what are you going to do? Whose house? Are you staying the night? Are you going to a club together? Will there be alcohol / drugs - are you cool with that? Who is handling the contraception, what barrier methods are going to be used? Is it &quot;just&quot; sex or will there be BDSM play?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There are a few options for multiple partners.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;ONE OFFS&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;One Night Stands - Either as a couple or as a single person hooking up with a couple. Naturally, there will be an element of weirdness as you are all new to each other and the sex therefore may Not As Advertised. Take time to get to know people and make sure that someone else knows where you are going to be that night (safety first, kids!). &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Orgies / Sex parties / Swinging Parties / BDSM clubs - Read the house rules. If anything is unclear, check beforehand. Follow the dress code and the play code (if there is one) and follow protocol. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;ONGOING RELATIONSHIPS&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This is a MASSIVE topic. Basically you are looking to have an ongoing relationship (not just fucking, but with emotions and all that jazz) with more than one person. This means you will get ALL the good and bad bits of a monogamous relationship, multiplied. &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There are loads of ways to do this. Use the golden rules and decide for yourselves what works for you. This will not stay fixed - relationships will grow and develop. And you will grow and develop too! Along the way there WILL be problems - like in any relationship - jealousy, loneliness (yes, really), upsets...&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;But the rewards are amazing.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Here's a few handy links:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Ethical Slut - useful book to read&#xA;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.amazon.de/Ethical-Slut-Infinite-Sexual-Possibilities/dp/1890159018&quot;&gt;http://www.amazon.de/Ethical-Slut-Infinite-Sexual-Possibilities/dp/1890159018&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Opening Up - good book on opening your relationship up to others&#xA;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.amazon.de/Opening-Up-Creating-Sustaining-Relationships/dp/157344295X&quot;&gt;http://www.amazon.de/Opening-Up-Creating-Sustaining-Relationships/dp/157344295X&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Good community and organisation for all things poly!&#xA;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.polyday.org.uk/&quot;&gt;http://www.polyday.org.uk/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="176" LastEditorUserId="176" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2012-01-20T13:14:49.390" LastActivityDate="2012-01-20T13:14:49.390" />
  <row Id="154" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="142" CreationDate="2012-01-20T12:52:47.330" Score="0" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;I've often thought that the adrenaline rush contributes a lot to sexual enjoyment - so the feelings you get from the &quot;fear factor&quot; especially in play that involved sensory deprivation, anticipation of knowing &quot;something&quot; is going to happen later but not what that might be all add to the satisfaction...&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="176" LastActivityDate="2012-01-20T12:52:47.330" />
  <row Id="155" PostTypeId="1" AcceptedAnswerId="161" CreationDate="2012-01-20T20:08:03.177" Score="1" ViewCount="30" Body="&lt;p&gt;I have tried a couple of time, but i didn't seem to work too well.  How should one perform oral on a woman to ensure that it's satisfying?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="118" LastActivityDate="2012-01-24T14:10:22.943" Title="Proper way to perform oral on a woman?" Tags="&lt;oral&gt;" AnswerCount="5" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="156" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="150" CreationDate="2012-01-21T00:23:50.470" Score="1" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;HIV in the early stages is not detected by standard blood tests. It takes a few weeks after infection before it can be detected, it's one of the reasons regular STD checks are recommended.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="48" LastActivityDate="2012-01-21T00:23:50.470" />
  <row Id="157" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="155" CreationDate="2012-01-21T00:27:55.830" Score="2" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;There is no one correct way, some people prefer different teqniques. As with most physical skills the best way to learn is by doing. Have a practice with your partner and ask for honest feedback on what works and what doesn't. (I'm sure she won't mind you trying :) )&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="48" LastActivityDate="2012-01-21T00:27:55.830" />
  <row Id="158" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2012-01-21T17:25:09.987" Score="0" ViewCount="22" Body="&lt;p&gt;Anticonception has been around for a long time. Currently there are a number of methods available that are based on drugs, timing of sexual encounters etc... What are the less common methods of anticonception that have been historically used and are in some form effective?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="60" LastEditorUserId="174" LastEditorDisplayName="" LastEditDate="2012-01-23T00:54:20.397" LastActivityDate="2012-01-24T14:21:09.743" Title="What are the less known, traditional methods of anticonception?" Tags="&lt;anticonception&gt;&lt;alternative&gt;" AnswerCount="1" CommentCount="3" />
  <row Id="159" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="155" CreationDate="2012-01-22T05:36:03.180" Score="0" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;Make sure it doesn't smell bad down there. If so, talk it over with your partner.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Once you have a clean and fragrant &lt;em&gt;garden&lt;/em&gt;, you can just do anything to your heart's content and everything will please her.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Remember smoother, softer, slower, and wetter strokes are better.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="154" LastActivityDate="2012-01-22T05:36:03.180" />
  <row Id="160" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="155" CreationDate="2012-01-22T13:32:02.557" Score="0" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;As with all these things, everyone likes something slightly different. More pressure here, slower, faster, whatever.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Your best way to do what your partner wants is to pay attention to them, their movements, their sounds etc., and talk with them to ask what they like.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="79" LastActivityDate="2012-01-22T13:32:02.557" />
  <row Id="161" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="155" CreationDate="2012-01-22T17:35:07.183" Score="4" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;Every one is different, which is why every one likes slightly different things done to them.  Not only is every woman is different, but the same woman can have different preferences from one session to another.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Some techniques I've found that tend to work:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Use the mouth/tongue to stimulate her clitoris.  Swirl around, and if you can curl your tongue so it forms a tube from front-to-back, do that and put her clit inside the curl (once she's been warmed up and is feeling good already, don't lead off with this technique, because it will overstimulate).&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;If she is so inclined and your hands are clean and you don't have long, sharp nails; then sometimes inserting a finger to play with the G-spot is also fun for the woman.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Pay attention for signals that she's having a good time.  &lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Moaning is occasional and usually right at orgasm.  Porn movies tend to have women start to scream in &quot;ecstasy&quot; as soon as he looks in her direction.  As the comedian once said, &quot;Yeah... that's in the movies.&quot; &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;As she nears orgasm, there will be body twitches, in my experience usually head and arms, but sometimes the legs will also. &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Be on the lookout for building tension.  When my wife is nearing orgasm, she gets quiet.  and her torso starts to tense up.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Held breath.  I don't understand it, but I've seen more than 1 woman hold their breath for a few seconds right before orgasm, usually with a sharp intake of air before doing so, and repeating until after the orgasm&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The infamous head grab.  Happened to me a few times.  Very rare.  Apparently I was on a good spot but moving off of it, and the grab was to hold my head right where it felt good.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Some things to look out for:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Target vision.  I understand combat pilots use this term to describe someone who starts shooting at the bad guy and ends up flying into the ground/other plane.  Here, be aware that if you do the exact same thing for too long, that part of her will start to become desensitized to that type of friction.  Mix it up.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Don't do it if you are rushed for time.  You may not be trying to short-change it, but you will still be and she won't enjoy it.  If you only have time for a quickie, then do a quickie and leave the head for another day.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Dirty hands inside her.  She tends to get UTIs much easier than he does.  wash your hands right before starting.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;stubble.  If you are a guy, feel your beard with the back of your hand.  If you want that sensation rubbing around your penis, then you are either masochistic or have a soft-enough beard to give oral.  I have a full beard, and find that I can't/shouldn't for a few days after even trimming it (since the hairs are sharp once again).&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;sharp nails.  I have the luxury of a long term relationship that has settled into when I have a good idea when sex will be happening.  As a result I'll trim my nails a day or two ahead of time. &lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="83" LastActivityDate="2012-01-22T17:35:07.183" />
  <row Id="162" PostTypeId="1" CreationDate="2012-01-22T17:45:33.563" Score="0" ViewCount="8" Body="&lt;p&gt;I'm a part of a relationship that is committed and monogamous.  I want sexual relations between 3-5 times a week, my spouse wants something closer to 1 or 2 times a month.  My spouse is a great match to me in all other facets of my life, but this one area is really causing us a bit of trouble.  She feels like I'm constantly pestering her, I feel like she don't care about me because of the lack of desire.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;How do we fix this?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="83" LastActivityDate="2012-01-22T22:39:38.013" Title="How do you handle partners with different levels of desire in a comitted, monogamous relationship?" Tags="&lt;long-term-relationships&gt;&lt;desire&gt;" AnswerCount="1" CommentCount="1" />
  <row Id="163" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="162" CreationDate="2012-01-22T22:39:38.013" Score="0" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;Having sexual relations does not necessarily mean that you have intercourse. Oral sex and digital/manual sex (handjobs/fingering in layman's terms) are two options that you should consider if you haven't already, and having your spouse perform these on you (with your reciprocating when she desires it, of course!) would not require her to be sexually aroused if she is not in the mood for it, but would allow you the intimacy that comes from being with another person. Mutual masturbation can also help a relationship, and if she doesn't want to participate, you could ask her if it's alright if you do so next to her or while she's in the room.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You might also see what you can do to get her in the mood. Massage and foreplay are by no means underrated; also, learn about and utilise what you know of what turns her on and how she likes things.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Anothoer option (if the previous two fail) includes sex toys. I don't want to make assumptions about your gender, since you don't say, and neither does your profile, so I will just say that they can be very useful both for solo use and with a partner, no matter how you identify. If you're female, there is a plethora of different toys available. If you're male, they're not just for cisgendered women to use; there are plenty of ways for men to stimulate themselves, too, including (but not limited to) cock rings, fleshlights, and cock sleeves, as well as various kinds of anal stimulation, which is not just for gay men, as many people believe (in fact, not all gay men enjoy anal sex at all). As a starting point, Good Vibrations (http://www.goodvibes.com) has a large number of options, and there are many other online venues available if you're interested.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A third choice is to discuss a nonmongamous relationship with your spouse. I am aware that you described your relationship as monogamous, and I also stress the discussion aspect of this. If you choose this route, be honest with her; tell her the issues that you're having (although if you haven't done that yet, you definitely should!) and see if she might be open to the prospect of you attaining sexual gratification elsewhere. This is something that many couples will not consider, but it can greatly improve someone's well-being. Sex Advice columnist Dan Savage has a lot to say on this topic (he describes it as &quot;monogamish&quot;), and one of his recent columns had a number of letters from couples who benefit from it: &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.thestranger.com/seattle/SavageLove?oid=11412386&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;http://www.thestranger.com/seattle/SavageLove?oid=11412386&lt;/a&gt;. There are quite a few other columns in the archives that discuss the same issues, as well.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I do hope this helps!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="179" LastActivityDate="2012-01-22T22:39:38.013" />
  <row Id="164" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="155" CreationDate="2012-01-24T14:10:22.943" Score="0" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;If you want to do some &quot;academic&quot; research before going down on your partner, &lt;a href=&quot;http://rads.stackoverflow.com/amzn/click/0446690902&quot; rel=&quot;nofollow&quot;&gt;this book&lt;/a&gt; will give you a few useful tips. A friend of mine wanted to learn the art of oral sex and I can tell you from personal experience that the tips are quite good... ;)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="184" LastActivityDate="2012-01-24T14:10:22.943" />
  <row Id="165" PostTypeId="2" ParentId="158" CreationDate="2012-01-24T14:21:09.743" Score="0" ViewCount="" Body="&lt;p&gt;An ex-boyfriend of mine used to belong to one of those military branches that don't officially exist. He wouldn't let me near his huge binder with recipes of natural poisons but I did manage to get an abortion recipe from his other binder with herbal remedies. Two of my girlfriends have tested it and found it effective. However, I'm not posting it here. Send me an email if you're interested.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;" OwnerUserId="184" LastActivityDate="2012-01-24T14:21:09.743" />
</posts>